[music]
>> If you support Barcelona, if you love La
Masia, if you love Messi, I don't think
anybody can lose, but most of the world
is going to be rooting for Spain.
>> YEAH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> HELL YEAH.
>> Hell yeah.
>> Most of the world is going to be rooting
for Spain.
>> Why would most of the world be rooting
for Spain when everybody wants to see
Messi
>> No, no, no. I'll tell you now, all of
South America is rooting against
Argentina.
>> Oh, for sure.
>> For sure. Let's stop with that. I'll
tell you now, all my friends from
Colombia, all my friends from Brazil,
South America is going to be rooting
against Argentina.
>> Whether it's Michael Jordan or Muhammad
Ali or Joe Namath, there there is a
history of guaranteeing victory. So, I
ask you, does Spain win the World Cup?
>> In English?
Yes.
>> From blowing kisses to sticking out his
tongue, Lamine Yamal's younger brother
has been going viral during the World
Cup. Ken, who is thought to be 3 years
old, has been spotted in post-match
celebrations and has become an
unexpected breakout star of Spain's
World Cup run with moments like this
after win against Belgium capturing the
attention of millions.
He also pops up regularly on Yamal's own
socials and he's reportedly attended
every Barcelona game, the club which
Yamal plays for, and was even at the
2025 Ballon d'Or ceremony with him.
Before his last World Cup match, Yamal
spoke about how much he loved his
brother.
>> I am proud of my little brother, and I
know when he grows up, he will be happy
of what I do, and I like that people
love him like I love him. And when he's
on camera, I like to see him.
>> HERE'S THE FINAL TOUCH OF THE GAME. HE
HAD THE DECISIVE TOUCH AS WELL. SPAIN,
FOR THE SECOND TIME IN THEIR HISTORY,
HAVE WON THE WORLD CUP.
>> Your final score from New York, New
Jersey,
in the 2026 FIFA World Cup final.
>> [cheering]
[cheering]
>> This is so funny. Spain edited Donald
Trump out of their World Cup photos.
They posted this on Instagram, the photo
went incredibly viral, and as you can
see, there's no Donald Trump on that
side. They also did the same thing on
Twitter using this photo again, where
Donald Trump is nowhere to be seen. And
what's also interesting is that the
official FIFA World Cup account on
social media posted a photo where Donald
Trump also isn't in it. They also edited
him out. Yesterday's game was great, the
World Cup was a fantastic tournament as
always, and the cherry on top is the
fact that Spain edited him out of the
photos.
>> Now, for those who are wondering, Donald
Trump was there.
>> [music]
>> Yeah, he was there.
>> Uh awkward.
Hey guys, welcome to uh another
Mercury in Retrograde Shadow Period
edition of Blue Centric Live. Thank you
for your patience. For those of you who
were reading the chat in the pre- in the
waiting room before we started, we're
starting much later than I expected.
Funny enough, I was actually finished
early today, but I am traveling, and you
know, for those of the girlies who
believe in retrograde, traveling during
retrograde always means that you have to
have the patience of Job from the Bible.
Yes? And when I was traveling, I was
like, you know what, Blue? Before you go
live, if you go live during your travels
and the lighting in here is horrible, by
the way, but it's not doing me any
favors. But, if you go live during your
travels, make sure you test the internet
speed before you go live because we're
still in the shadow period of
retrograde. So, sure enough,
sure enough,
I checked the speed the speed of the
Wi-Fi in this hotel was abysmal. For
those who are not tech-savvy, in order
to go live, you need at least 100
megabytes, right? 100 megabytes mean we
can have a decent conversation. The
hotel was at 12.
Which means a horse and buggy was going
to be running the internet, and I was
like, no, I'm not about to go live and
spend the entire live talking about,
"Can you hear me? Can you hear me?" So,
I called to the front desk. They
transferred me to that third-party
technical support team. Um a man named
Suraj
in India. I'm not being racist. I said,
"What's your name?" He said, "Suraj from
India." So, this is what he told me.
Suraj from India spent 40 minutes trying
to help me with the internet and by the
time he was done it was worse.
Actually, we started at 44. We got to 12
after he did whatever he did in India.
So, guess what guys? We're reporting
live to you from my hotspot. For those
of you like Blue, why do you have so
many phones? Well, these phones are
going to be
I'm running the entire live on my
hotspot. At this point guys, I'm
camping.
I'm camping. Yes, 12 means that spider
monkeys are just on a wheel climbing up
a wall trying to get Yeah, it's bad. It
was real bad. I wasn't about to do y'all
like that. So, it's so funny. Somebody
said in the chat, "Blue's bad luck with
hotels during retrograde." First of all,
everybody has bad luck with hotels and
travel in general during retrograde. I
will tell you though, I want to shout
out somebody before we start today's
show and start talking to you guys about
First of all, we're going to talk about
the World Cup. As you can see from the
intro, um somebody put in the chat, "As
a Latina, it feels crazy having to root
for Spain." I agree. That's why I did
that intro. For those who don't
understand why people from Latin America
feel a way that they find themselves
Yes, as a black Latina, hello.
We are here, right? Me having Vívela
Asa, me having to root for Spain in the
World Cup felt funky to me and to my
American brothers and sisters who are
not a a part of the soccer fandom,
although many Americans I want to give
y'all some credit are getting more with
football, right? Than previous years.
Um
it felt nasty having to root for Spain.
I wanted to first start off with the
pro-black love story of the star player.
I'm not going to try to mispronounce his
name. Me and vowels don't get along. Um
him and his brother's love story about
how his brother was his biggest fan when
he
when he ran into it First, he fell to
his knees and prayed to God, then he got
up and ran to his brother's arms. Like
it was so beautiful. So, I thought
focusing on black boy joy would be the
first way
that we would get the bad taste out of
our mouths for having to to root for
Spain. Cuz what in the Christopher
Columbus
Okay, as me and someone for those who
don't know my lore, I'm Haitian and
Cuban. My half siblings are Cuban and
Dominican. So, Hispaniola and that whole
sordid ordeal, me and Spain got beef. Me
and France got bigger beef though.
Respectfully. Me and Spain got beef. So,
having to root for Spain felt funky. So,
for the 40% for those who are new, 60%
of you come here are well informed and
just come here to hear about things that
you already are well versed in. 40% of
you come in here to hang out and spend
some fun with us and and learn. So, for
the 40% who don't know why black
Americans, black Latin people, black
people in general, people who can read
history books, we all felt a way that we
had to root for Spain
despite the Columbus of it all.
I'm going to do a quick history lesson
to kick us off before we get into the
mess. Cuz you guys know we believe in
edutainment here. And shout out to all
the people who are sending silver Oh,
silver star, I've never seen that. And
gems and such.
I love when you guys sell gems cuz I see
the flow state. It's really fun when I'm
watching the replays. But shout out to
all the new people who are coming and to
all the returning people who are family.
Um before we talk about the Netflix
trend that has many of your fair-skinned
faves getting yanked cuz it didn't occur
to me until I made the
um the thumbnail. I was like, "Wait, now
all the girls who are getting in trouble
for the Netflix trend all look like
cousins." Did y'all notice that? Am I
the only one? It did not hit me when I
was conceiving of this. I was just like,
"Oh, three different people have gotten
in trouble for doing the Netflix trend.
Let's talk about it." And then when the
when the when the thumbnail went up, I
was like, "Oh, they're all from the same
tribe. That's awkward." We're going to
get to that in a second. But first, a
quick moment of edutainment about why
this World Cup was particularly
conflicting for the well-informed black
and brown people amongst us who know
that Spain be on some [ __ ] but
Argentina is worse. If you want the
short of it, if you have a low attention
span, and you want the short of it,
Argentina's worse.
That's really what it comes down to.
It's like, imagine you had to root for
either your least favorite
uh oppressive boss or the conglomerate
that is taking over the town. They both
suck, but one just sucks a lot worse,
right? So, quick history lesson, let's
get started now cuz I feel bad for being
so late. Although, shout out to Siraj
from India, you did a horrible job, but
you were you sounded kind on the phone.
I'll give you credit. Um if you're new
here, please like and um subscribe.
Consider being a member because if you
were following me on Threads, you'll see
we're going to be talking about
Nickalandria in the members-only
section. We're also going to be talking
about something else that I'm not going
to mention. Members,
we'll talk about when we get there,
right? But in the members-only area,
we're going to talk about Nickalandria,
and then we're going to do something
else that I'm not going to talk about in
gen pop. And so, if you're not a member,
this is a great time to do so. If you
are a member, get some snacks. We're in
for a long night. It's going to be fun,
though, I promise. All right, let's
continue the history lesson. My dear
sisters, I know you're about to be
disgusted with me this weekend for
rooting for the OG colonizers, but it
needs to be [music] done.
Still very present in my mind, you know,
what they did to the indigenous people
of the Caribbean, you know, the
enslavement and the genocide and all of
that. You know, yes, Spain has enslaved
people in the Caribbean, right?
Um lots of genocides, lots of bad thing
I mean, all I have to do is say
Christopher Columbus, right? So, many of
us There's many people who were on
Instagram praying to their ancestors,
this is a necessary evil, please don't
smite me down in my sleep.
Yes, I do be taking care of the members.
Shout out to the members. I love y'all.
I mean, I love the rest of y'all, too. I
just like the members more. Um cuz it's
a family, right? But I need y'all to
understand this this video. I saw
Filipino people because Philip
You think the Caribbean people got
problem with Spain? Filipinos have been
done dirty.
Even Filipinos find themselves having Do
you know how bad Argentina has to be for
Filipinos to be rooting for Spain? We'll
get to that in a second. Have you seen
what Argentina's been up to? Have you?
Okay, okay, before you judge me, just
know the Filipinos are rooting for
Spain. Yeah. The
And Spain did them in the worst way.
>> [music]
>> That's how you know it's bad.
>> But hear me out, 15th century Spain.
Boo! Evil!
>> Yes, they have an N-word burger in in
Argentina.
We have receipts. By By the way, shout
out to This is what I always say to my
Dominican brothers and sisters who who
catch strays. In the same way that if
you are a pro-black Dominican, um it's
possible to recognize your country's on
some [ __ ] and still be on the right
side of history, but also recognizing
that, you know, your country's on some
[ __ ] Look, I live in America. As an
American, I'm constantly having to apply
that's my [ __ ] country. So, I get it.
So, in the same way that I love my
friend Rosa Acosta because she's a very
vocally pro-black Dominican who does not
make excuses for the Dominican Republic
and still is proud to be Dominican but
recognizes they're on some [ __ ] If
you're up from Argentina,
do the same thing.
There's no way to cover this up. Your
country's on some [ __ ] Own it, and
then show us through actions that you
know better.
>> Hater.
Modern-day Spain.
>> Promethazine. PROMETHAZINE, OKAY?
>> We're not forgiving or forgetting the
crimes Spain and their conquistadors
have committed against us, right?
We're just saying that Argentina is a
present dark evil force that needs to be
vanquished.
>> Argentina is evil in the present tense.
We're talking about history. Argentina's
evil like today, like Tuesday, the 22nd
of July.
>> And Spain is the only one [music] who
can do it.
>> Time for anything from your examples
that we must never ever allow evil to
prosper.
>> For those who are saying you hope
Nikelandria News is a fake out to be
left alone, um
we'll discuss that in members only. I'm
not saying [ __ ] about Nikelandria and
and Gen Pop, but yeah, we'll discuss
that.
>> Thank you for your understanding.
[music]
>> And if you would like to sprinkle some
support to Spain, okay, all right, too
much, too much. ALL RIGHT.
CLEARLY, THEY'RE MAD.
>> NOW, THIS IS THIS IS SPEEDY, ONE OF the
world's most, if not the most, popular
active streamer besides Kai Cenat.
He was literally invited by FIFA, okay?
The people who do the World Cup, the
World Cup called Speedy and said, "Black
man, get your ass over here." And still
you would think with that much clout,
because you know, there's some people
who are racist, but they'll be nice to
you if you have clout.
I live in LA. I can tell you stories
about that [ __ ] But you would think
that somebody with as much clout as one
of the if not the top streamer in the
world, you would think him being there,
he would get some No, they started
making monkey noises at him.
They started throwing food and cans at
him. They started calling him the N-word
while he was live streaming, y'all.
That's how much Argentina has normalized
racism in the present tense. Yes, they
did him so dirty. It was
It It actually made me really scared for
his safety. I'm not going to hold you.
>> Chat, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT, Y'ALL.
BRO, STOP THROWING STUFF.
Y'ALL GOT TO LISTEN. Y'ALL JUST GOT TO
RELAX. Y'ALL DON'T GOT TO THROW STUFF.
IT'S ALL LOVE.
>> ARGENTINA'S TEAM has been labeled the
most racist and hated team at all of
FIFA.
But why?
>> So we're going to go over this, and you
guys know how I am. I can say something
as a racially unambiguous black woman,
and y'all think I'm just being a mean
bitter black [ __ ] but let me find
somebody who looks like you who says the
same thing, and suddenly it makes sense.
So I've intentionally picked
people across the the Latin diaspora of
varying degrees of Cuz my version of
Latin, you know, y'all got a problem
realizing that that Latinos can be black
and nappy-headed, okay?
I know because of propaganda, you think
that all Latin people look very
Aryan, okay? Blond hair, cur- like I I'm
I'm clear what y'all think Latinos are
supposed to look like. So just know,
we're going to have the entire diaspora,
cuz it's very rare that we're all on the
same page.
It's very, okay? I'm I'm going to I'm
going to enjoy this moment while I can.
Yes, it makes me angry, too, my love.
It's very rare that Latin America You
know how bad you have to be for Latinos
to call you racist?
Can we sit with that for a second? Do
you know how disgusting you have to be
for a Latin people
as a whole call you racist?
At that point, you are pre-Nazi.
So, I just need you to understand how
bad it was. Like, it's it's The World
Cup was almost like a quick education on
who our modern-day villains are.
>> I'll tell you why.
>> Tell me why.
>> Historically, we know they genocide and
ethnic cleanse entire indigenous
population of their own land. Then they
mass murdered by 40% of the black
Argentinians down to less than 1%.
>> are mean.
>> Then for some reason, they invited Nazi
war criminals to live there freely.
>> For some reason, they did a mass
genocide that got their black population
down to only 1% and then invited Nazis.
I'm going to stop saying that word so I
don't get in trouble, but
I feel this is not even a complicated
story time.
>> While increasing the European population
to 97%
or most people would say
>> That it has nothing to do with them,
boludo.
>> But it's embedded in them. In 2022's
World Cup, Argentinian fans are filmed
once again doing racist chants to black
French players, claiming they're not
French because
>> they're black.
>> Call them Africans.
>> Two years later, 2024 Copa America, it
wasn't the fans this time, now it's the
players. So, on the team bus, Enzo
Fernández livestreamed this. His own
Chelsea teammate, Loïc Badé, Fofana, a
black Frenchman, reposted it and wrote,
"Football in 2024, uninhibited racism."
FIFA investigated, Chelsea's team opened
disciplinary proceedings, Argentinian
sports minister said Messi should
apologize, and guess what Argentinian's
president did? He fired the sports
minister that said Messi and the team
should apologize.
>> That doesn't even make any sense.
>> Messi obviously never apologized. Nobody
part of the Argentinian team apologized.
The only response that anyone got was
the Argentinian president saying nobody
can tell the national team what to
think. Then in the 2026 Champions
League, Argentine player Gianluca
Prestianni allegedly called Vini a
monkey five consecutive times while
covering his mouth with a jersey. The
match stopped for 10 minutes. Mbappé
confirmed he heard it. There are a
couple Benfica players that heard it,
too. His
>> Imagine you're playing on the biggest
stage in the world and the entire time
you're trying to focus you're being
called a monkey.
>> same team. And Prestianni's defense?
>> I didn't say anything racist, my dude. I
only said something homophobic.
>> Here's saying it's low, I'm saying.
>> Reminds you of that one Argentinian girl
that also got arrested this year for
making monkey gestures and noises
towards a black guy in Brazil. And she
was a lawyer, so this is someone that's
educated in Argentina. And just about a
week ago at this year's World Cup,
Argentina versus Cape Verde at the Miami
stadium, an Argentinian fan was caught
on IShowSpeed's livestream making monkey
gestures towards him. Mind you, he's a
young successful black kid that was
invited from FIFA directly to livestream
here, and these people do not give a
[ __ ]
>> You see how we're showing receipts? So
this is not a matter of opinion. At this
point this is a matter of fact. We're
saying water is wet here.
>> FIFA condemned it and launched an
investigation, but trust me, nothing's
going to happen. Then in 2021,
Argentina's own president Alberto
Fernández said this on camera standing
right next to Spain's prime minister.
The Mexicans came from India. The
Brazilians came from the boats from
Europe. The
>> The Brazilians came from the jungle.
Now, we all know cuz I've said this
several times and so has Google.
We all know that outside of Africa,
Brazil is the blackest place on Earth.
So,
y'all don't find it suspicious that they
keep on saying Brazilians came from the
jungle? We Do we understand Do we all
hear that dog whistle?
The blackest place on the planet,
literally outside of Africa, Brazil is
Wakanda.
For the For the person who's saying
Roxane Lewis, who's saying as someone
who was an Argentinian fan, I'm shocked
by the way. I was clearly living under a
rock. Roxane, this is why we do this,
right? This I will tell y'all right now.
There is a
person, a white man that I I was
compared to a lot back in the day. It's
This is a very obscure reference. So, if
you're one of the 12 people who even
know who I'm talking about, raise your
hand, put a little blue heart. There's a
man who had a show called I think his
name was Adam Conover or something like
that, cuz you guys know I'm bad with
names when it comes to vowels. But, Adam
had a show called Adam Ruins Everything.
And what Adam would do is he would take
things that you thought you knew and
then tell you the truth.
And you'd be like, "Ah, [ __ ] That's not
what I thought. My bad." And I had a
friend back in the day who loved that
show. She's like, "Bitch, you are just
Adam with titties. You are Adam."
Because there are so many things that we
are taught to not question that I
question all the time. Shout out to the
autism, right? And so, just know that if
you come on this space and you find out
that something that you used to clap for
it was on some [ __ ] don't feel bad.
It's kind of the premise. The premise of
the show is while the powers that be are
trying to make us stupid, there is a
vocal minority of us who are trying to
do the opposite, right? We're the
counterculture who are trying to do a
counter-balance because while they're
making the world stupider. As a matter
of fact, guys, I've said this a million
times, research has showed that there's
a cognitive decline that happened after
millennials, and I don't think it's
because the kids are stupider. I think
it's because the machines have gotten
smarter and are intentionally making the
kids stupider. The kids and their
parents, okay? So, because we are
literally literally, as a matter of
fact, not opinion, in a collective
cognitive decline, as a matter of design
not happenstance. I do feel like there's
some sort of responsibility for those of
us who are educated on topics to share,
right? Yeah, we are family here. So, for
anybody here who was an Argentina fan,
please don't feel ashamed. For anybody
who's Argentinian and not racist. Number
one, shout out for being a statistical
anomaly. Number two, don't feel bad,
just do better, right? Whatever you
learn today, I'm asking you to share
with others who might not know. All
right, let's continue.
>> Fact that he was comfortable say all
this should tell you everything you need
to know. So, when people say they don't
like Argentina, when Latino say we don't
claim Argentina, when they say Argentina
is European not Latino, when
Argentinians say "They're just jealous."
It's not about football. Messi's not
even the best player from Argentina.
It's about your nasty despicable history
and how you choose to keep it alive to
this day being proud of it. And like
anything, this isn't all Argentinians.
>> By the way, y'all don't think it's
again, you don't find it suspicious that
while Brazil, second blackest place on
Earth, cannot stand Argentina, Brazil is
the big brother to that always protects
Haiti?
The blackest first free black republic
in the Caribbean. You don't see the line
here?
Pro-black nations. And here's the thing,
Brazil as a whole is not always
pro-black. Brazil's got its own
[ __ ] But Brazil is also so black
that even if the government is
anti-black in any kind of way, there's
just too many [ __ ] to shut them up,
okay? It's too many of them, yes? So,
the the contrast to Argentina is Brazil.
When Haiti lost to Brazil, you couldn't
even tell who won because there was so
much love. They were hugging each other,
right? When Brazil and Haiti were
fighting, it was like you playing
dominoes against your favorite cousin.
The love that Haiti was shown after a
loss by Brazil made me emotional cuz it
was a reminder of what it looks like
when black people don't let the powers
that be convince us to fight amongst
ourselves.
Conversely,
Brazil told Argentina to suck its dick.
I don't know how to say that nicer,
sorry. Yes? And Argentina, when
Argentina lost to Spain, they turned
their backs. They wouldn't even watch
them as they took their their their
victory lap. They are poor sportsmen and
racist. So again, Argentina,
I I'm I'm going to take some time before
we start the actual show. Don't worry,
there'll be timestamps for y'all who
just came here for the mess, but I'm
going to take some time before we start
the actual show just to let people know
how much you suck. Cuz it's my show and
I can do that.
>> But it is most Argentinians. Well, what
do you guys think?
>> Girl, did you know that Messi's team has
quite the reputation for being racist as
hell? Just a couple days ago at the
World Cup, Speed, one of the most famous
streamers on Earth, if you've never seen
him before, was literally getting
berated by Argentina fans and getting
told to go cry at the zoo. Wonder what
they mean by that. And allegedly they
were calling him a negro. And it's not
abnormal for Argentina fans. I'm zooming
in on her cuz she cuz she was really
going hard. So so y'all can see her
face. But it's not abnormal for
Argentina fans to be doing racist [ __ ]
like making monkey noises at black
players and doing racist chants and like
don't listen to me cuz I know how y'all
get. Go look it up yourselves. It's not
just the fans either. Enzo Fernandez,
after winning the Copa America 2 years
ago with Argentina, went live on the bus
and why were him and his teammates doing
a racist chant about the French team and
their black players being of African
descent but playing for France. They're
making fun of them for being black.
And before you say I'm reaching, his own
black teammate from Chelsea came out and
posted that it was uninhibited racism.
So So this is when you start asking
yourself, why does it seem like every
other Latin American country has beef
with Argentina? Why does it always seem
like Argentina is at the center of a
racist scandal? If you look at Argentina
today,
>> So guys, for those who were asking about
the dogs, the dogs are what we play to
cleanse our chakra after heavy topic.
Don't worry, I finally found the dogs.
So we're we playing the the chakra
cleansing dog chime after we do this
history lesson.
>> You'd be like, there's not a lot of
black people there, especially in
comparison to other Latin American
countries where there are a lot of
Afro-Latinos, right? Well, in In 1800s,
Buenos Aires was about a third black.
So, you can't say that there were never
any black people.
>> Y'all know how much a third is? That's a
lot of [ __ ] people.
That means one out of every three people
in Buenos Aires back in the day was a
black person. If you go to Cuba,
Cuba's black as hell. People are like,
"Blue, I didn't know you were Cuban. I
thought you were black." I said, "Baby,
you've never been to Cuba." In Cuba,
they all look like me. Cuba's black as
[ __ ]
>> Well, so what happened to us?
>> Us as in black people. But in Argentina,
I'm not from Arge Y'all get what I'm
saying? So, what happened to black
people in Argentina? I'm going to give
you straight cuz this is a history
class.
They sent black men to fight in wars so
that they would die. They sent black men
to die in war, literally, the
government. Um again, look that up. I'm
not
>> By the way, doesn't that sound a lot
like what America's trying to do with
the draft?
It's almost like history just repeats
itself until you learn it.
There's nothing new under the sun,
especially with the Trump
administration. So, for for our my
American brothers and sisters, please
pay attention.
>> making this up. And then, a disease
outbreak obviously disproportionately
affected poor black neighborhoods,
literally wiped out poor black
neighborhoods. And on top of that, the
cherry on top,
they invited a bunch of European
immigrants
to Argentina to literally whiten up the
population and stopped counting black
people in their censuses.
They they just ignored the black
population altogether. They erased their
black population like they never even
existed. So, of course, you push that
narrative for 100 years and they're
like, "Well, we're basically Europe. We
don't have black people, so there is no
racism." And that
>> By the way, Dominican Republic's
uh through their president Trujillo
tried to do the same thing, but because
Haitians and Dominicans are all like
related, it's a lot it's a lot harder.
It's a lot harder to do it in
Hispaniola. The Well, I keep on saying
Hispaniola to be provocative cuz you
know, Spain won. But, um it's a lot
harder with Haiti and Dominican
Republic. Dominican Republic did try to
do the exact same thing. Um I think the
moment when Trujillo tried, a lot of
Latin nations have tried to whiten the
the nation and had it as a matter of
law. Look it up, right? Argentina's just
the most successful and the most
persistent.
>> That's the problem. And then if you look
at a country like Brazil that has major
beef with Argentina, it's no mistake
that Brazil got more enslaved Africans
than any country on Earth. So, when they
tried that whitening up Brazil [ __ ]
there were too many black people for
that to even work. Same continent, same
era, completely different outcome. So,
yeah, while this is one of the most
popular teams in the World Cup and I'm
probably going to get jumped for making
this video, I can't not think about this
every time I watch them.
So, I got to root for whoever they're
playing against. My bad.
>> And guys, for those of you who are like,
"Well, Blue, that's history. That's the
World Cup." Baby, we in Atlanta now,
okay? I want I was like, "Blue, how do
you bridge the gap for anybody in
America who's not into football, I I eat
soccer, and who's like, why should I
care?" Baby, this is Atlanta.
The Argentinians showed up to Atlanta
and tried to uh
[ __ ] with the Atlanta blacks and learned
real quickly we don't play that [ __ ]
Watch this. This is crazy.
>> What the [ __ ] is Andrew doing in there?
He's a foreigner.
>> Do you understand? Imagine you're just a
black man in Atlanta minding your
business, going to brunch cuz you you're
a black man in Atlanta, of course you're
going to brunch. And a man with a thick
accent rolls up to you while holding a
baby and just starts calling you the
N-word.
Where they do that at? And then the man
holding the baby has the audacity to be
shocked that you want to beat his ass.
>> That's a [ __ ] child.
I can hear it.
>> Meanwhile
>> You know what's crazy about this video?
I intentionally didn't play for the walk
so you guys could really orient with
what you're looking at cuz there's so
much mess.
Yeah, the he's a foreigner, all that
stuff. People who are taping it are a
white couple who finds this funny.
They think the black man is the one
who's wrong because how dare you attack
somebody while while holding a baby?
My question is, if you didn't care about
the baby when you were being racist, why
do you care about the baby when you when
it comes to the consequences? That's a
real question by the way.
Y'all know how I feel about virtue
signaling. We're about to use that word
a lot because y'all have been doing it a
lot and I'm going to keep calling it
out. But you use something virtuous as a
shield from [ __ ] That's what virtue
signaling means, right? It means you do
some [ __ ] and then when somebody
holds you accountable for the [ __ ]
that you started, you say, "Well, I'm
the bigger person. Why can't you be the
bigger" [ __ ] you weren't the bigger
person when you started this mess. Not
too much, right? So, to virtue signal
while I'm holding a baby, how dare you
react? Baby, you were holding the baby
when you said the thing, though. Like,
why won't you think about the baby?
The white folks are laughing.
Keep an eye Now guys, I will say this.
Why am I showing this? Here's the thing.
I actually thought about do I want to
save up my coins and go to the World Cup
the next time it happens? And then I saw
a video saying that you had to pay
$9,000 for nosebleeds.
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm not I'm not playing
paying that. $9,000 for for nosebleeds
and Beyoncé's not going to be there?
If you thought I was rich, this is your
your moment to know I'm I'm not rich
enough. I don't I don't make enough
money where I can spend 9K to be in the
nosebleeds. So, any kind of FOMO I might
have had about being at the World Cup
went out the window when I started doing
research about that was up against me.
RIGHT HERE,
>> GETS PUSHED.
>> SO, THERE'S A MAN, A BLACK MAN, walking
around with a Mexico shirt, right? Shout
out to the Mexi- my Mexican community. I
live in LA, so I feel like to be
anti-Mexican while living in LA is is
audacity, okay? And so, there's a black
man in a Mexico shirt, and the
Argentinians, one of them is from New
York, says like, "Yeah, whatever."
Starts yelling at him at at him or
whatever because he's a black man and
he's representing Mexico, right?
The guy that's with her
forgets that they're not at home and
starts saying the N-word on camera.
>> You remember her?
Listen, dude over here is having fun,
but just listen now. Listen.
>> So, the black man is saying, "Fuck you,
I'm going to choose Mexico over
Argentina. Are you crazy? Hell, that's
not even that's not even difficult." And
they lost their
Once they start being racist, he's like,
"Why y'all taking it this far? I thought
we were just talking [ __ ] ABOUT
FOOTBALL."
>> YO, YO, YO, don't pull a race card,
[ __ ]
>> [ __ ]
Don't pull a race card, New York, baby.
Y-
know how I feel when y'all use being a
New Yorker as an excuse to be ignorant.
As somebody who lived in New York for
for
a larger part of a decade, please stop.
I feel bad for New York, especially, you
know, Mom Donny's town. Please stop
using being a New Yorker as as an excuse
to be a basic [ __ ] I hate when y'all
do that [ __ ]
>> Hey, we ain't [ __ ]
DON'T YOU CALL US THAT.
>> OH, YOU HEARD THAT?
>> SO, for those who didn't hear, he
started yelling [ __ ]
He started yelling the N-word. And even
the New York baby, even she was like,
"Oh, [ __ ] we were supposed to pretend
we weren't racist on camera. What are
you doing?" Now she's trying to shut him
up from being who she is.
>> You heard that?
>> [ __ ]
>> And one more time? One more time for the
camera?
One more time?
>> Many are wondering why folks from the
global majority, Latinos, people of
color, were not rooting for Argentina
and don't feel bad that Argentina lost.
This is because of stuff like this. I'm
not saying that all people from
Argentina are like this, but this is a
pattern. We saw it in the aftermath.
Here's another example. Homie over here
might be a little obnoxious, but he's
having fun. Whether his goal was to
irritate them or not, there was no need
for this lady to put her hands on him,
and this man was waiting for any
opportunity to show his anti-blackness.
Unnecessary, uncalled for, and
absolutely disgusting.
>> Argentina thinks that it's not racist.
>> So, this is the final word. I want you
guys to I'm going to end this with a
final bit of just history to tie it up
for cuz I know people come late, so I
intentionally chose some history facts
at the beginning and now at the end. So,
if you're late, don't worry. This is me
catching you up. And then we're going to
end with an account of a black man who
went to Argentina, and you could tell
the black guy in the video that we're
going to show after this one,
in his mind, he's trying to convince
himself it's not all Argentina. It just
so happens to be bad luck that he ran
into some racist. I'm going to play that
video cuz black people, I need y'all to
stop excusing racism to show people that
a team player. Please stop. Any team
that needs you to excuse racism or
downplay racism to be a team player, to
be a good sport, is not a team you need
to be on. But first, one more history
lesson.
>> Because uh Argentina thinks that there
is no black people.
>> In Argentina, blacks do not exist.
That's a Brazilian
>> Sexyy Red was born in Argentina?
>> [sighs]
>> I'm going to pretend I didn't even read
that. I'm going to pretend I didn't even
Yes, we're going to be talking about um
Nikola Andrea in the members-only area
because the violin fans are like to
tussle and I don't have the energy. So,
that's going to happen in members only.
It's not going to happen in gen pop.
>> and problem.
>> That was Carlos Menem, then president of
Argentina in 1996.
>> It is said that it's the whitest country
in South America, that it's the Paris of
of America of Latin
>> It's the Paris of of Latin America.
>> America Argentina is not white, you
know? If not, if not, I wouldn't be
here.
>> But Menem didn't invent this myth. He
was repeating a narrative built over a
century of deliberate racial erasure
because history tells a different story.
[music] As early as 15
>> My heart aches for black Argentinians.
If you're a black person with
Argentinian roots, like I That must That
must be like being a Jewish German
person. Like it must be rough as hell to
be a black Anybody with black ancestry
from Argentina who actually claims it.
>> 1588, enslaved Africans [music] arrived
in what is now known as Argentina.
Between the 16th and 19th centuries,
more than 200,000 enslaved Africans were
brought to the region. A 1778 census
found that approximately 1/3 of the
country's population consisted of people
with African descent. In 2022, less than
1% identified as Afro-descendant. So,
where did they go? Some historians point
to disproportionate black conscription
in Argentina's wars and a devastating
1871 yellow fever epidemic. Though
others argue these were secondary to the
deliberate policy of erasure by the
state. In the late 1800s, Argentina's
leaders decided the country's future was
European.
>> You see how the picture start off very,
very color like people of color, black,
brown, like all types of mix and then as
the pictures go on they get whiter and
whiter. You guys, like we need to stop
pretending like this is foreign. Anybody
who's watched an NBA draft
Yes, balling there.
The NBA is America's version of
Argentina.
Let me know when y'all ready to have
that conversation.
>> They called the policy blankeamiento,
whitening, [music] and actively promoted
intermarriage and mass immigration to
dilute the non-white population.
>> We don't think that one blood one drop
of blood makes us uh black. We think
that one drop of blood makes us white.
>> Around
>> In Argentina, the one drop rule works in
the other way. One drop of white makes
you white not one drop of black making
you black. That is
Ooh, bon jeur. That is a lot of
self-hatred. That is some very low
racial self-esteem.
>> 7 million subsidized immigrants, mainly
from Spain and Italy, arrived between
1850 and 1950. While black and
indigenous people [music] were pushed
out of the public record.
>> The Argentinian state created a new um
racial category, trigueño, that means
from the color of the wheat.
And that made black people invisible and
in
>> From the color of the wheat, which is
their version of saying brown paper bag
test.
Y'all see how history, wherever you go.
That's why I want to tell people all the
time like Yes, be proud of your country
and also recognize that there's some
[ __ ] that is universal. This is one
of them.
>> indigenous people [music]
>> Erasure on paper was met with violence
on the ground. Between 1878 and 1885, at
least 14,000 indigenous people were
killed in the so-called conquest of the
desert in Patagonia. In July 1924,
Argentine police and settlers massacred
the Qom and Mocoví people who were
protesting inhumane living and working
conditions on cotton plantations in
Napalpí. Between 400 and 500 people were
[music] killed, and it took until 2022
for it to be called a crime against
humanity.
>> Uh indigenous people, they ask them,
"Where are they from?" Uh
and and they're from
Argentina. From there, more Argentinian
than in fact they are they been here
before Argentina exists.
>> Do you hear this? The indigenous people
who were there in Argentina before the
European settlers are being treated like
they're outsiders. Is that not Native
Americans here?
You guys see how many similarities there
are? It's actually kind of insane. I
think one of the reasons why Diaspora
Wars feels intellectually stunted to me
is cuz as the more you study history,
the harder it is to act like national
lines separate us and that and that you
our shared humanity means nothing,
right? There are so many things that are
very specific to different countries,
but there are so many evils that are
universal. And I I think this is
illustrating that. So again, if you are
someone who is black, brown, an ally,
someone who thinks that you are proudly
on the right side of history, and you
felt a way about having to root for
Spain, I think this is kind of my way of
saying maybe it really was the lesser of
two evils. I get it.
>> system.
>> Even Argentina's most famous export
[music] carries this history of erasure.
>> And we don't know that tango comes from
milonga that came from African slaves.
>> Tango, the roots of tango, which is what
Argentina is very proud of, is rooted in
Africans.
Ain't that about a [ __ ]
>> music. We don't know that. We We don't
We say just it's Argentinian. We are
here that we didn't die in the wars that
and we are black and we are Argentinians
and Argentina is black. [music]
>> Argentina
What did I tell you? And I keep telling
you and telling you again and we get
more footage every day. Yet people still
defend them.
>> What's a place you would never go back
to though?
>> I would go back everywhere but a place
that I wouldn't pay like if that bread
right they say hey we want you come out
here and promote this. I'm going to get
the bread but I wouldn't necessarily
want to go back to Argentina.
>> Did you hear how okay the mental
gymnastics this man is doing? He said
I wouldn't go back for free but if they
paid me I'd sell my soul to the devil
because if the bread is good [ __ ]
racism. I need y'all to understand I
intentionally chose this clip. For those
who are apologetics again, I need you to
see the mental gymnastics it takes to be
this intellectually dishonest rather
than just say they don't [ __ ] with us.
Rather than admit that he was
uncomfortable in Argentina, he stutters
and says well what place wouldn't I go
back to? Well, I would go back to
anywhere for a check.
But the check would have to be real good
in Argentina.
>> Unless it was somewhere
unless it was somewhere different but
I didn't see like I didn't find
Argentina super fun.
I did and I was there for a long time
too. I was there for like a month and a
half. So I wouldn't necessarily go back
there.
Um
>> Was the people cool or like
>> was cool man but I mean I did have
racist experience. Somebody called me
the N-word there.
>> For what?
>> Man cuz we wouldn't like bro it sounds
stupid but we wouldn't watch
a football game with them like we was
walk we was leaving the stadium.
Uh the soccer stadium we was leaving a
football stadium and we were walking
around and they was like oh what's up
like a group of 30 30 people on one
little bitty ass TV watching and they
was like y'all come over here and watch
with us. Come over here and watch." And
we was like, "Nah, we we about to you
know, we about to slide somewhere else."
Shout out to my boy West. We about to
slide somewhere else.
And then they was like, "All right
then." Like they was on some [ __ ] like,
"All right, [ __ ] y'all then." And we was
like, "All right, whatever, man. We not
finna Y'all 30 deep. Y'all beat our ass
for real, you know what I'm saying?" So
we just kept walking. And then they was
just saying every slur that came out.
Like they was like, "Bitch! Bitch!"
>> So 30 impoverished Argentinians invited
you to watch football with them. When
you said no, thank you, they immediately
started attacking you and making monkey
noises and calling you the N-word and
calling you a [ __ ]
But it's no big deal though.
>> "Bitch! Nigga!" And then we turned
around and we was like, "What?" And then
they was like, "Yeah." And I was like,
"All right, y'all got it this time cuz
it's y'all 30 deep. Like y'all We ain't
dumb." But um
yeah, that was the only racist thing
that really happened like ever in my
travels for real.
>> That wasn't enough for you not to go
back?
>> And it was just like they wasn't like
that animosity don't it don't really
If If somebody calls me the N-word, it
don't really hit the same unless they
like a white American for some
>> So now he's saying, "Well, their racism
doesn't count because they're not white
Americans." Yo, bro, I need y'all to be
freed from these shackles.
I need y'all to be freed from this.
>> reason. Like you [ __ ] is
No disrespect. You [ __ ] is poor. Like
Y'all more of a [ __ ] than we are, dog.
Like Y'all watching a beat-up TV and
with 30 people plus. But um I've had
I've met I say that, but I've met so
many I still have so many Argentina
friends who I met along the way from
there
that show love. And they like, "Bro, I
hate that that happened, blah blah blah.
You know that ain't us." And I was like,
"Man, it's some of y'all, just not every
all of y'all."
>> You see what it looks like when someone
makes apologies for things that are
blatantly unsafe in a world in the wake
of what happened to Nolan and what's
happened to many others, I fear for
black people who take that stance, who
think that they're different or above
it, and then find out the hard way that
we all [ __ ] to the wrong people,
right? So, that was my quick history
lesson on Argentina. I'm going to take
this down real quick and play the chakra
cleansing dogs. Now, we're going to
pivot with the timestamp of 44:24. We're
pivoting to our our main topic, which is
Netflix, and how that trend that we all
thought was fun has taken a turn for
some of our sisters.
>> [music]
>> Okay, we sprayed the air, guys, okay?
We've cle- Ooh, it smells good. Jesus,
that smells good. We've cleaned the air
from all that [ __ ] that we just saw.
And now we're going to pivot to Wait,
has everybody here I just want to make
sure we're on the same page. Has
everybody here seen the Netflix like
joke documentary where you sit down and
pretend that you're getting miked up to
be
um in a Netflix doc, right? If you
haven't seen it, you're going to see
plenty of examples right now.
So, many people have done this. And I
remember a couple days ago, not a couple
weeks ago actually. Damn, time is flying
by.
A couple weeks ago, I was doing a
podcast with someone from um Trevor
Noah's old talk show. And her the
podcast when it comes out, I'll let you
guys know. And she and I are doing the
podcast, and when I do the clip for it,
I was like, "Oh, I need a sound effect."
And at the very top of trending topics
was the Netflix um audio because it was
trending so much, it was the top audio.
So, I just kind of threw it on there. I
don't even think we did it right, but it
the audio was so popular, it's easy to
say, "Oh, I'm going to join in the fun."
Now, I'm shooting bell because I'm
saying, "Okay, I know what it's like to
not even be thinking about the trend,
but anytime you're online, they're
shoving it down your throat, so it's
easy to want to join in.
Some of our faves and some of our not so
faves have tried to join in and um
they've had messy results.
The first person that I saw having messy
results from joining
on this uh whole trend. Oh, you came
right on time. Yes, you did. 44:24 for
those who are doing timestamps in the
the chat. I'm going to keep repeating
this so I remember to do it myself.
44:24 is when we started. Um we're going
to start with Tia of Tia and Tamera
fame. She did the Netflix trend and they
started whooping her. Now, here's the
thing, guys. Tia has always been seen as
the darling of the black community while
Tamera was the darling of the
conservative MAGA community cuz she's
married to a white man who works for Fox
News.
But however, y'all turned on Tia.
Maybe I'm late to this party cuz I don't
know everything. I know sometimes you
think I act like I do I think I do, but
I don't know everything. I was stunned
that y'all turned on her for joining the
doc. So, let's see why the girls are in
a tizzy cuz again, the girls look like
they're tussling, honey. But the girls
are mad at Tia because apparently her
shading her sister apparently and her
shading her sister is up for debate. But
they think she shaded her sister and
they're mad at her about it.
>> I've been seeing a lot of people do that
trend where you sit down and you pretend
you're on that on that Netflix
documentary Surviving blah blah blah.
Now, I'm about to be brutally honest. I
haven't seen anyone's post
that had me actually wanting to see
their Netflix documentary.
Only one person
one single person
has done a video for this trend and I
was like, you know what?
I would actually press play on that [ __ ]
so [ __ ] fast. This right here.
This right here. Do you see that?
>> And the the the caption says, "Me when
Netflix makes a documentary about having
the same face but completely different
lives."
I I thought we all knew they were
completely different. I thought that was
part of the joke. I'm I'm I'm a little
confused.
>> It's the completely different lives for
me.
It is it's it's it's it's very telling.
Oh my gosh, cuz we all know Tamera is
married to that white man.
So.
This is the one I would watch.
Immediately. Netflix, make it happen.
>> Can you hear me?
Are you ready?
>> [music]
>> Well, let me tell y'all what happened on
TikTok today, right? So,
Tia put one of those messy little TikTok
things up with the documentary thing.
You know how everybody been doing that
trend or whatever. So,
she got up there and the documentary
post said,
"When you have the same exact face as
somebody but a [clears throat] totally
different life." So, I commented and I
said,
"Black twin, now why are you sitting up
here being messy?"
>> [music]
[laughter]
>> Okay guys, you Okay, maybe I'm confused.
Do you think that's messy? I'm not I
actually don't have a strong opinion on
this. I was just surprised by the
backlash.
Do you think her simply posting
a documentary about how you and somebody
can have the same face
and have completely drastically
different lives, do we think that's
messy?
Somebody said, "I don't like being
called Jump Out Blue. I'm trying to work
you into my budget, my girl. I'm I'm I'm
coming blue crew. I'm a distant cousin."
I appreciate it, sis, but the other
people outside with you are a little
mean.
Just just know, I'm not safe outside, so
I have to call it something different.
>> Yo,
>> [music]
>> that [ __ ] had probably like
5,000 and something likes by the time I
saw it, right?
Why she deleted my comment?
>> Because she knew you were going to
create a a fire
>> So, I'm commenting as a twin on the Tia
and Tamera debacle that's been going
around. Uh so, those of you guys who
don't know, but everybody's online, I'm
sure you've seen it. The Tia posted um,
a a little video doing the Netflix
trend.
>> So you guys, this is from a twin, right?
And you know that sometimes when I'm
watching these And somebody said that
the sound was too loud on the video, so
I did turn it down. Let me know if that
works for you guys.
I don't hear the same thing you do, so I
appreciate the feedback. You guys, is is
the sound better? I lowered it a lot.
We're good? Cuz you guys used to
complain the sound was too low, and I
got so many many complaints last year
for the sound being too low. I always
turn it all the way up, but if it the
sound is now too loud, let me know. I'm
trying, child, okay? I just work here.
But I haven't watched this video yet,
but this is a video of a twin. So I
thought, you know what? We're going to
watch this together. A twin has an
opinion about twins, who better? Let's
see what she has to say about this.
Maybe she'll teach us something.
>> Where she says like when they do a
documentary series on having the same
face but living very different lives.
And obviously the context behind both of
them is the fact that a lot of people
have been supporting Tia in the black
community over Tamera for years because
of the fact that Tamera married a white
man who they claim was mad uh, and Trump
supporter and worked on Fox News and all
these things that I actually don't know
that much about. Tia and Tamera have
always been one of those twins that was
like staple household name, especially
in the black community. Like they both
were all on the same networks, the same
things growing up, the same movies. They
were act- they worked together actually
for such a long time. It was only
recently like in the 2010s that they
started going their own way.
Um, so for people to kind of claim
Tamera or I mean to claim Tia over
Tamera has been always kind of weird to
me and say that Tamera is more white or
whatever because like they got They were
always like in the same stuff. It's just
who they married obviously was
different.
In certain things.
>> But what they married is drastically
different. One of them married a black
man.
And my By the way, this is not to name
drop, I ran into
uh, to uh, Tia's uh,
now ex-husband Cory
um, in June of 2024 because we all were
at ABFF cuz that was the year that Issa
was the ambassador, and many of you
know, I'm friends with a lot of people
who are in the Insecure graduating
class, right? Cuz a lot of people who
left Insecure went off to do amazing
things, right? Amy Aniobi is an amazing
director. She directed, I think the last
two seasons of Survival of the Thickest.
Mike Gauyo, you guys know Mike. I love
Mike. He's now famous for all his Love
Island producer videos. He's one of my
closest friends. He was a writer in the
show room. He went off to do Ginny &
Georgia. He's now doing his own shows.
Um, Sarita Singleton who was in that
writer's room, she is is the one who
wrote that movie um with uh Kiki and
SZA, um Just One of Those Days that did
great at the box office. We were all so
proud of her. Jean Elie, we've seen him
on on the the Members Only chats. He's
popped up. Monique's husband Richard
plays Molly's brother. Like that whole
ecosystem
of Issa's people, and this is going to
come up later when we talk about Amanda
Seales. It it's going to come up later.
But that whole ecosystem of the people
who work with Issa Rae and who came from
the school of Insecure have now gone off
to do amazing things. And so we all,
when we found out that Issa was going to
be the ambassador for the American Black
Film Festival back in June 2024, we all
kind of went there to be supportive and
to hang out. It was an amazing time, by
the way.
Cory was there and this was like 5
minutes after it had really broke that
him and Tia broke up. He was nothing but
kind, uh very gentle, very charismatic,
very like chill, not trying to be in the
spotlight. And however, and and we have
mutual friends who said nothing but kind
things about him. Some of my favorite
people, oh I love that you love the
show. Shout out to Amy Aniobi. Um, but
people have said nothing but kind things
about him. And however, comma, you could
be a lovely person and still be a
horrible husband. So just because I
think he's a lovely like just decent
human being in a social circles, doesn't
mean I purport to know who he is as a
husband. However,
Tia was married to a black man for about
20 years, right? They were together for
decades. Conversely, while you're in a
black on black love relationship, right?
Cuz y'all love to talk about black on
black violence, but you don't talk about
black on black love. Um, your sister is
dating a white man crying about being
biracial even though you both look
exactly the same. And so she's not
realizing that some of her biracial
issues are not because can we be honest
Tia and Tamera just look light-skinned.
There's They're not even all that
racially ambiguous. They're the kind of
light-skinned that if they tell you
they're biracial you'll believe them.
And if they tell you you're black you'll
also believe them. So it's not like they
were walking around, "Oh, I wonder what
you are. I got to squint." Nobody's
curious about if they're black or not,
right? So as two fair-skinned black
presenting biracial girls, while one is
investing in being pro-black in the
optics and in her real life, the other
one is dating a white man crying on TV
about being called the white man's
[ __ ] and the white man she's dating is
not even an ally. He works for Fox News.
So this is not me throwing tea at Tamera
cuz she cuz again, siblings say shady
[ __ ] So you finding a video of someone
saying something shady to their sibling
is not going to make me gasp. It's just
that I don't understand why her
acknowledging that they're they live
drastically different lives
is offensive and messy. And this is me
not feigning confusion. I really
I really don't understand why it was
that wording that pissed everybody off.
There's so many other things Tia has
done where y'all have been mad at her
and I'd be like, "I can see how well
that's messy." This though, you know
what I'm thinking guys? I'm thinking
maybe it wasn't this. It was those of
you who were already sick of her because
during the divorce y'all were like, "Tia
is a [ __ ] who left her husband. How
dare you leave this good black man?" Cuz
Cory was a good black man, but how dare
you leave this good black Y'all got sick
of her for getting a divorce. So maybe
some of the people who are already tired
of her, this was the straw that broke
the camel's back. But the straw on
itself its own
doesn't feel heavy. But I'll let this
lady cook. I want to listen with an open
mind.
>> about their personalities, I guess. But
to be honest, they both kind of were
quirky to me. They both always gave girl
next door. Tia a little bit mild-spoken,
but nothing about her specifically
except for who she married gave that she
was a blacker twin in general with them.
Anyway, all that aside, the saddest part
about seeing this whole twin debate
between them or this like thing that
Tia's kind of starting or propagating is
these are twins and I don't think if you
don't obviously if you're not a twin you
don't understand like being a twin is
the same DNA, the closest person to you
on the earth like person who has shares
same genetics as you, looks the same as
you, probably thinks and feels very
similar to you if not exactly. Um
obviously nature and nurture plays a
huge role, but because of how similar
twins are, the bond usually is very very
strong. The fact that even the kids are
usually half siblings. It's a very close
bond.
>> Mhm.
>> If I met somebody who treated their twin
a certain type of way, as someone who
was a twin,
I would be scared to be friends with
that person, no [ __ ] no tea. Because if
you can treat your twin, identical
blood, DNA, similar, whatever, like
that, then how you going to treat me,
boo? And even if you feel like, "Okay,
as a friend that I I'm closer to you,
maybe like you feel like I have similar
ideologies to you." That's still very
concerning to see someone treat another
human being that's their blood.
>> Someone said, "Yes, Blue. They didn't
like her since the divorce. Some didn't
like her before, but um she posted can't
be super happy content pretty much. It's
odd to me." Look, I'm going to let you
guys are allowed to have your feelings.
I
I'm just trying to understand more so
than disagreeing. I just don't get it,
to be honest.
>> their own twin, their own sister like
that.
>> Mhm.
>> Things that pop up a lot as being a twin
is that people try and put you against
one another.
Some peo- Some people are just, you
know, jealous of a twin bond like oh,
like you have someone that's that's that
close to you. I don't have siblings or I
don't have siblings or I don't have a
friend that's that close. And so some
people will try and put your sister
against each other. But for me,
especially me and my sister, we have
always seen that when we try and put
somebody in between us or we let someone
get in between us, like it ultimately
ends up biting the person who did it in
the butt because it's like now you see
that the The who didn't like your twin
most likely did it doesn't like you
either cuz if someone's going to try and
ruin your your sibling bond like that,
they probably don't like you. If someone
really cares about you, they'd want you
to prioritize and maximize your
relationship with your sibling. So, we
That was when we were younger, mind you,
like elementary school. Since we've
grown up, we don't ever let anybody get
between us, even if it is family
members, like
>> I understand what she's saying that
um
the twin bond is really sacred and so
anyone who tries to intentionally break
you up with your twin, that's a red
flag. I could see that. And though,
however, comma, what part does
>> [sighs]
>> impact have on that? If you have a twin
who is laid up making life with someone
who is MAGA and not just MAGA quietly or
privately, but somebody who is a
spokesperson for MAGA on the biggest
MAGA network in the world and you're
someone who If you guys look at Tia's
new boyfriend, he is something straight
out of 2008 when Jill Scott was taking
long walks and we were all wearing jean
jackets. She's dating a crunchy granola
black man who probably smells like Noam
Chomsky and likes to grease her scalp.
She in another super black relationship.
The kind of woman who is in a super
black relationship who only loves black
men, who is the only person that BET
wishes happy birthday to every year and
the other sister doesn't even get a
shout-out. Someone who's that super
black
if they had some complicated feelings
about their sister who is in the belly
of the beast
is being a twin enough not to show that,
though?
I get it. What she's saying, I get in
general.
But to be mar- not even dating, to be
married to and procreating with a MAGA
pundit in 2026
while I am pro-black
and very much for my people, I can see
why Okay, let me I'm going to keep I'm
going to keep listening. I really want
to give it up in my mind, so I'm going
to keep
>> talk it out because we understand that
at the end of the day like that's the
closest person on this earth to me. So,
why would I let somebody people over
what? Likes? Over clouds? Over even even
romantically? Like even letting a
romantic partner get in the way of our
bond is something that we would never
let happen because that's crazy. Like
you just met that person relatively
speaking. So, it is really sad to see
that what's going on with Tia and
Tamera. I really hope that Tia reflects
and thinks about the things in her life
that's making her act that type of
>> Yeah, but there's an infamous tweet of
BT saying happy birthday Tiamari and
then here's Tamera in the comments like,
"Hey,
the [ __ ] We're twins. Yeah."
It's been a running joke for years. It's
been and and honestly, if you've seen
Tamera on The View, not The View, what's
what's The View uh leftovers? The Talk,
is it The Talk? The people what's that
show called when the four girls were
pretending to be The View?
The Real. There we go. The Real. I know
it was the something. On The Real
them girls could not be any more
different.
>> she's been doing this since the TV show
and I know that because I re-watched all
the shows um episodes recently and I was
very gagged to see like
she was actually worse back then. Um
she's more subtle with it now, but like
it's crazy to see like your own blood,
heart, and soul getting in the way of a
bond that
you know, should not be broken.
>> But isn't being a MAGA getting in the
way of the bond?
I'm sorry y'all. I'm trying so like
y'all don't understand. I family is so
important for me. I'm in Boston [ __ ]
doing the show with a hotspot on my on
my on my phone because family means so
much to me. I drop I drop everything
once a month to come see my family and
check on them, right? I understand
caring about family. I get it.
Everything I do is for my family. And
Uh
okay. I'm going to just What does white
lady got to say? Let's see what she got
to say.
>> People are saying Tia is a narcissist
and that she hates her sister Tamera and
that Tamera should just block her. Are
people losing their ever loving mind? If
you know anything
>> Wait, not the white lady coming to the
defense of the pro-black one. Okay, we
in the down.
Now, hold on. Not Not the black lady
spent all this time acting like being
MAGA is not a big deal and that's the
white lady. Y'all Every up is down, down
is up.
I chose Y'all know how I choose videos.
I want to experience it with you.
I chose a twin cuz I wanted to hear from
a twin.
I chose the white lady cuz she had good
graphics and she seemed like she was
well researched, but didn't listen to
her.
I even have a clip with of Tia talking
for herself. But, I hadn't expect for
the black lady to be
anti-Tia and for the white lady to be
caping.
This is why I don't say I'm rooting for
everybody black. I'm rooting for
everybody pro-black cuz some of the
people who are rooting for us don't even
look like us, child. This is a weird
It's a weird time to be alive.
>> about me, you know that I've been
obsessed with Tia and Tamera. I watched
Sister, Sister, Style Network show, The
Game, The Real, all of that. And I've
worked with them twice. And here
>> Oh, you were staying from the inside.
Okay, well, [ __ ] give us some tea.
Let's see what happened.
>> everyone is missing. First of all, this
all started because Tia jumped on the
Netflix trend where you're sitting down
for the documentary and she wrote, "Same
face, completely different lives." And
then people lost it in the comments. So
much so that Tia had to write, "Guys,
it's just a trend." At the same time,
Tamera said she found out that Tia got a
reality show just like everyone else
online. And everyone thought it was some
sort of plot against Tamera. But then
Tia responded and was like, "This is
just normal sibling stuff." And listen,
this has always been their dynamic. Like
we saw them have friction when
Tia told Tamera that she booked in a
movie, The Mistle-Tones, and asked Tia
if she was jealous. Then when Tamera
wanted her best friend to be her maid of
honor a long
>> You marry a white man from Fox News
and you ask somebody else to be a maid
of honor.
I I Hollywood is different than real
life, but this is, y'all I think this is
bigger than a Netflix spoof.
I think she's been weird. I think she's
been weird.
>> Side, Tamera was jealous. We saw them go
to therapy because they had
communication issues. And Tamera even
said their relationship got strained as
soon as they stopped being roommates.
And when Tamera was a new mom, Tamera
would leave her to go be with Adam and
his family. They had different
priorities. Here's the other big
difference between these two which I
think has created even more friction.
Tamera marries Adam. They have a
vineyard. Tamera can work or not work.
>> Wait, they have a vineyard? So Adam's a
rich white? Oh.
Tamera, you married a rich a rich white
Republican from Fox News.
Oh, so he has power to be a part of the
[ __ ]
He's not even a bystander. Like he's
like in into the thick of it. He's in
the thick of it.
Not Uncle Luke. Y'all are hilarious. Um,
Huh.
Okay, this white lady is making me look
at Tamera more crazy than Tia. I'm
sorry, y'all.
I mean you my vitamins, don't judge me,
but
I was trying to keep it open mind, but
the more y'all talk, the more I'm on
Tia's side.
>> Tia, on the other hand, marries another
actor, Cory. She gets pregnant. She has
two kids. Cory, I don't think he's that
nice to her. I think he's rude to her.
Just me personally from what I've seen
on TV. So then Tia gets a divorce and I
remember Tia saying to Tamera, "We don't
all have the luxury of not working." In
other words, her sister gets to cruise
on by and be a mom while being provided
for by her husband and Tia is now a
single mom supporting two kids with an
ex who may or may not be providing
support. Do I think Tia's a narcissist?
Absolutely not. I think they lived half
of their lives together and when they
separated, they became different people.
I think it's hard for Tia to watch
Tamera have an easier life than her and
I think she wishes she could call her
sister and vent, but
>> Okay, I don't I don't [ __ ] with Adam,
but them kids are beautiful. Those are
some beautiful kids though.
>> she can't relate to her sister and I
think that adds another element of
difficulty. I also think Tia prioritized
their relationship whereas Tamera is
prioritizing her marriage. So here
>> Imagine if
Who's that pretty lady
who's um old uh in her 40s but looks
young? Tamika
from um
Black Lives Matter. What's her name?
She's very cute.
What's her name?
Tamika Mallory? Yes. Imagine if Tamika
Mallory and Candace Owens were cousins.
I'm being extreme on purpose. If Tamika
Mallory and Candace Owens were cousins,
would we be shocked
if they weren't close given how Thank
you. Would we be shocked if if if the
white lady actually uh came with some
sense? I'm not I'm I'm I'm going to give
her credit.
Y'all know I'm a follower of truth
wherever I find it, okay? The blonde
lady ate with that. But if Tamika
Mallory and Candace Owens were cousins,
I would not be shocked or think Tamika
Mallory was a Judas for not [ __ ] with
her heavy and throwing shade sometimes.
Wait, Tamera called her daughter the
dark one?
That baby look like creamy creamy light
coffee. Okay, you know what? Let me
stop. I'm about to get mad.
>> My question, when you get married, who
becomes your first person? Is it your
spouse or your sibling? Let me know what
you think in the comments.
>> You talk about your sister.
>> Okay, so we're going to end with Tia
talking for herself cuz cuz maybe I
still don't get it.
I'll let everybody argue their very
long-winded points.
I still don't get why y'all mad at Tia.
Somebody said And this is a good case
study of being twins grow Oh, that's
Midsen. Hey Midsen.
And this is a good case study of twins
growing up in the spotlight. We only
have a few examples of what that does to
their relationship long-term and don't
know all of the things they face. True.
All right, let's let's let's hear Tia
talk about this
in her own words.
>> No, on the show.
>> Yeah, she's just not as accessible, but
I literally [music] just talked to her
yesterday.
>> Okay.
>> She is a mother. Her children need her.
She is also a wife. Her husband needs
her.
>> She's in a different [music] place in
her life. She wants to do her thing and
I'm doing my thing.
>> It's the same thing even with my
brother, you know, we were doing movies
together, 17 again.
>> I think the reason why people [music]
tend to go there is because our careers
started together. Just like any sibling,
like everybody goes off to do their own
thing and and you want them to. You want
them to be individuals and to fly solo.
So, there's nothing, you know, harmful
[music] in any of that.
>> Y'all, on this docket, I I I'm going to
I'm sorry.
I think I think y'all need to cut our
girl Tia some slack.
Y'all know Y'all know that being a black
woman is not enough for me to cape for
some [ __ ] Again, we follow the
truth here wherever we find it.
I I I think Tia is innocent.
I think Tia was trying to have a fun
moment, saw that y'all wanted to get
mad, cuz again, the girls like to tussle
these days, and said, "Oh, it's not that
[ __ ] serious." and stepped out. She
probably regrets even posting that
[ __ ] video. Unless she was looking
for the engagement, but still.
On the case of Tia, I think we're going
too far. All right, next case on the
Netflix doc uh trend going wrong docket
is none other than Amanda Seales. Let's
do this.
>> [music]
>> It's fine.
It's fine.
>> What is this wig?
What is this wig?
By the way, guys, for everybody who
called me anti-black
for having eyes to see that Aniya's wig
was matted in the back. I need you to
understand it's not anti-black to notice
somebody has a matted wig.
Matted wigs are not a secret tenant of
black culture.
That feel like a backhanded something
that y'all think that that ignoring
a matted wig
means you're pro-black and and and
noticing a wig is matted means you're
anti-black.
What do y'all really think anti-black
means? What sacred facet of
anti-blackness is matted hair?
Just It's very bizarre. And funny
enough, while y'all were calling people
anti-black for noticing that somebody's
wig was revolting, nobody said anything
about the still I rise jokes that they
were constantly making at KC.
Again, very weird.
I don't think y'all know what some of
these words mean the way that you use
them, but Amanda put on
this unit
because she was mocking the fact that
Tiffany DuBois, her her character that
she plays from Insecure, was not going
to be on the Insecure tour.
For those who don't know, Insecure is
now going on tour, and Amanda used this
trending topic as a moment to say, "How
dare they not invite me?" All right.
Damn.
>> [music]
>> Okay, so I don't know if you guys know,
but Issa Rae in Insecure is doing a
10-year reunion tour of the show. So,
when they put the
ads videos out to promote the tour, of
course, Amanda Seales, who plays Tiffany
on Insecure, is not included in the
reunion tour. So, yesterday she made a
video. You know, they've been doing the
Netflix documentary trend, so it's like
Tiffany DuBois' Netflix doc about not
being on the Insecure tour. Now, I don't
know if you guys remember, but some
months ago, or maybe even last year,
Amanda Seales went on Shannon Sharpe's
podcast and she basically was like, "I'm
done
>> Y'all, she wasn't It wasn't a couple
weeks or months ago. It was April 24th,
2024. You know how I know? Cuz the
[ __ ] show came out on my birthday and
it ruined my birthday party cuz
everybody wanted to watch that [ __ ]
instead of helping me blow out the cake.
It wasn't a couple months ago. It was
April 24th, 2024.
>> "Protecting Issa, this is my story. She
doesn't like me. It was a difficult work
relationship." She tried to mend it, it
just didn't work out. They do not speak
anymore.
>> Mhm.
>> So, I was just confused cuz I went to
the post and of course she's in the
comments, you know, responding to people
saying she doesn't know why she was left
off of the reunion tour. She was
>> She doesn't know why? Can those of you
Yeah, [ __ ] up my birthday. But can
those of you who are Amanda fans explain
to me how Amanda doesn't understand why
she wouldn't be invited to be at a
function of people that she was talking
[ __ ] about? Why she always confused when
she's not invited in spaces where things
have been hostile and therefore not full
of camaraderie?
If the whole premise of the tour is
camaraderie and we are not comrades, why
would you be invited?
>> [sighs]
>> If you are a fan of Amanda Seales,
please without being snarky or nasty,
this is a sincere question. Please
Amanda was left [laughter] off of
Insecure. Every time I make that joke, I
laugh. Please explain to me
why anybody would think that they would
be invited to spend time with on tour
with someone who they've been talking
bad about for months,
if not years.
>> such a pivotal character. She was a main
character. And it's like, you literally
went around to multiple podcasts. You
were on Instagram live and all these
things not bashing
>> No, Amanda is going to We're going to
show a video. No, Amanda is a video of
Amanda saying that she thinks she should
have been invited. So, that's not true.
Amanda thinks she actually should have
been invited.
Joke or not, she came out and said she
thinks she should have been invited.
We're going to We're going to get to
that.
>> E said, "Not saying that her story's not
true, but it's like
you just complained about how five
seasons y'all didn't work well together,
but now you want to be included to work
on a reunion tour with her.
That doesn't make any sense. Like
>> It doesn't make sense.
>> If you don't like her and you're tired
of protecting her and you feel like she
don't like you and da da da she was
done, then why would you be on the
reunion tour? I'm confused as to why
that invitation would be extended to
her. Regardless of your title and role
on the show, you made
>> We're in the upside down again.
In no world am I Y'all know I come on
here and talk about people every day.
There's There's some people that I know
if I talk about you, I'm probably not
invited to your function.
And I understand that and I do it
anyways. Yes?
It would never occur to me
to talk about somebody,
to critique them
in a way that I know they could find
unflattering if not flat out
disparaging, and then be confused or
have an expectation that I'd be in their
space.
That's universal. That's not even just
about Amanda.
>> clear that like y'all are not cool.
So, I'm going to assume that Amanda
feels she was just joking and just
wanted to hop on
>> I do believe that might be the case,
allegedly. Just an opinion, it's not a
fact.
>> point.
Um that Netflix trend and you know, just
troll a little bit, but she knows
exactly why she was left off of Bad and
Boujee, okay? And for the people that
don't know, you need to Google. It takes
nothing.
All you got to do is look it up on here.
She don't [ __ ] with them like that and
they damn sure don't [ __ ] with her,
okay? Like you can't go around talking
about them and saying your experience is
in a negative and um thinking that
you're going to get invited to come back
when just about everybody didn't have an
issue with you.
>> Everybody.
>> Everybody else on the cast is still cool
with each other except for you. They're
not even cool with you. It's just E said
that's not cool with you.
>> By the way, guys, I'm not one of those
people who believes that
if one person
doesn't get along with the collective
then that immediately means that that
one person is the bad guy. Sometimes the
collective is toxic, right? There have
been so many toxic friend groups that
I've had to remove my friend myself from
cuz I was like, "Oh, you're all
collectively on some [ __ ] I'mma
head on out." Right? So, this is
actually I don't actually subscribe to
if everybody has a problem with you, it
has to be you. What kind of people have
a problem with you matters. If 10 toxic
[ __ ] don't like me, it's the
same problem being generated, right?
Now, if it's a toxic person, a
reasonable person, a healed person, a
non-healed person, a rich person, a poor
person, people who don't even know each
other, if 10 people of different varying
walks of life with no incentive have an
issue with me, then I'll be like, "Well,
[ __ ] everywhere you go, there you are.
It might be you."
But if the same [ __ ] on the same
[ __ ] don't like me, it's the same
problem being repeated 10 times, right?
So, I don't believe that a group versus
one means the one is wrong cuz [ __ ]
I'm usually the one. Yes? What I do
believe though, and this is why I
mentioned this earlier, when decent
human beings
who are decent human beings around
everybody else
who are paying you and have no incentive
to do you dirty because your happiness
is
actually helps them get further.
When decent human beings from different
walks of life who don't even know each
other
who are not comparing notes
who are cool and Gucci elsewhere
have a problem with you
then it might actually be you. Y'all see
the difference? Cuz again here, nuance
matters, yes? My issue was never that
Amanda had a problem with her castmates.
My issue was Amanda had a problem with
just about everybody. Some of these
[ __ ] don't even know each other. I
cannot tell you how many times I've been
out in LA and her name comes up and
somebody who ain't got nothing to do
with Insecure, nothing to do with Issa
Rae, nothing to do with Vanessa.
Cuz I again I have met all parties
involved. So I'm not speaking from my
side of the club, okay?
I've met folks who were gaffers, makeup
artists, random girls who worked in
craft services.
The only two people in this industry who
it doesn't matter who it is, it could be
a janitor or a CEO, I'm going to hear
something bad about them is Amanda
Seales and JLo.
I was on set for some [ __ ] that hasn't
come out yet recently.
And somebody who was putting powder
under my eyes started talking about JLo
and saying [ __ ] that I've been hearing
for years, okay? So just know at a
certain point, baby, it got to be a
little bit of you.
I'm just going to put that out there,
okay? All right, let's continue.
>> is you and you constantly talking about
her.
Um and your experience and I don't
really hear Issa bringing you up, Amanda
up, you know what I'm saying? And I
again she has every right to say what
went down
um in her experience on that set and all
of that, but we wouldn't
>> I'm autistic my as well. If you're if
you're harmful, being autistic doesn't
mean that you get to be harmful without
being checked or having consequences. I
disagree with that. As somebody who's
autistic, has ADHD, and an anxiety
disorder, I don't agree with that.
Weaponizing autism in order to to allow
people to to cause harm without any
consequences actually really dangerous.
>> I don't know anything going on if it
wasn't for her.
Y'all remember when she went to that um
party? This is when we first started
hearing about something going on when
she went to that party and she got
kicked out or whatever.
And she was mad that Issa didn't really
step up for her and stuff like that. It
was down here ever since then in the
public for her with them, you know?
And so
you going on different podcasts, you
talking about her
>> Vanessa is the is the rep that works
with Issa who's a She's a She's a She's
a
She's about her business, okay? Vanessa
don't [ __ ] play. You know how some
people you you just look at them and
you're like, "Oh, that [ __ ] don't
play." Which is why I'm very confused
why Amanda thought she was going to have
a a one-two back-and-forth with her. But
Vanessa works for Issa, and she's the
one who said
Amanda's not invited to this
after-party, and Amanda went live crying
outside the after-party because she
wasn't let into an event that she was
not invited to.
I might save this for the members-only
area, but I know Misha,
oh god.
I'm not sharing nothing that any of my
friends connected to Insecure have told
me. So this has nothing to do with any
of them. People outside of the Insecure
bubble who know what happened, who were
friends of Amanda, Amanda's old friends
have told me things.
Amanda, that lady was never going to let
you in her function. And And if what I
was told you did to that lady is true, I
wouldn't let you into my [ __ ] house,
either. Let alone a [ __ ] function I'm
throwing.
So just know that the things that made
the lady not mess with her were valid
things.
When did When did we start the
members-only? When did we start
members-only? We're starting it soon,
okay? Cuz this is getting harder and
harder for me.
>> their own platform or whatever. So,
yeah, girl, that's why you got left off
of Bad and Boujee. You don't like Issa
Rae.
And I don't care if you feel like your
character or a character was that
significant to the show or movie or
whatever. If you don't get along with
the people on there, they're not going
to The creator, the director they're not
going to bring you back, okay? That's
like having a problematic employee of a
company, and they get fired. Y'all have
an anniversary or a party or some [ __ ]
or whatever. And even though they
contributed 10 years there, they're not
going to ask them to come back and
celebrate. No, it don't work like that,
okay?
>> I've said this a million times. When you
are on set, you don't always pick the
person who's the most talented. You pick
the person who is talented and you don't
mind being stuck on set for 16 hours,
eight weeks at a time with. Do you know
how exhausting, mind-numbing, and
hellacious, and psychologically abusive
it is to be on set with somebody for 16
hours a day for weeks on end, who is
just a
a displeasure to be around?
When you see somebody who you think is
moderately talented get very far, and
you see somebody who is super talented
not get very far, sometimes it's because
people don't enjoy being around them on
set.
And it's valid.
You know what's killing me right now?
There are people who can't even sit in
the lunch room for 30 minutes with a
co-worker who has was rude to them one
time,
who are acting confused why people don't
want to be on tour with somebody who has
been nasty for years.
Are y'all okay?
Again, it's intellectually dishonest.
Many of you would have fought her, like
literally rolled up your sleeves and hit
her on the face for less. So again, I've
said this a million times, the lady is
brilliant. She is valuable. She She adds
value to the to the social commentary,
right? She is steeped in her purpose.
And her antics socially get in her way.
Those two two things can coexist. We
don't have to pretend that she's not
brilliant to also say that she has some
blind spots that she continues to avoid.
>> Like girl,
just continue doing what you was doing
on your little podcast, battling and
talking about everything else, and you
know, getting the
>> By the way, for someone who said I don't
understand why she wants to be in the
presence of people who she doesn't [ __ ]
with, that's exactly my point. You guys,
I've said this before, me and Bridget
had a very infamous now uh episode of
our pod where we talked about when I
went on tour with her and her former
podcast, and how that tour was the worst
experience of my life, and it's the
reason that if I go on tour with
anybody, all the terms need to be hashed
out before I agree to anything.
I'm never going on tour with anybody
unless I am guaranteed to be treated
correctly because of how much PTSD I had
from being on tour with Bridget and
Mandy, right? So as somebody who's been
on the tour, somebody who was a
displeasure to be around,
I wouldn't wish that on my worst enemy.
It's insane that any of you think that
Issa, who's in charge, needs to put
herself through that. I think it's
absolutely insane. I'm not even going to
pretend the other side makes sense.
>> People rallied us for whatever reason.
She is so exhausting. And And the thing
of it is,
I understand where she was coming from
cuz I do like Issa, right? But I'm not
the type of person that's going to
invalidate somebody's experience. You
know what I'm saying? Regardless of who
I like. I listen to everybody and I feel
like everybody has a right to say what
they, you know, went through, what they
feel and all that stuff because I wasn't
there. So, who am I to tell them that,
"No, you're wrong."
I like to validate people's stuff. But
at the same time, you can say what you
feel, expect, you know,
put out your experience, whatever, but
you have to be ready to take the
consequences for doing so.
>> Exactly.
>> I've said this before. I oftentimes
>> So, Dominique was talking about this. I
don't know what Dominique said, but I
always enjoy what she has to say. So,
maybe Dom You know what? Dominique has a
friendly relationship with Amanda. So,
I'm open. You guys Look, even on this
show, we stay open. I'm open to
Dominique maybe having an alt
alternative That's That's why I chose
her. I know that Dominique and and and
Amanda are friendly. So, if Dominique
has an alternative perspective that I
haven't thought about, I'm open to it.
But as of right now, this [ __ ] is not
even a Scooby-Doo mystery to me.
There's no [ __ ] way you're going to
talk about me crazy all the [ __ ] time
and think there's any way you're coming
on any [ __ ] I got going on. Are you
nuts?
>> will stay out of discussions around
Amanda Seales because there days I feel
like the people will compile um her and
I've met her and it was a pleasant
experience.
That being said, this is at the
intersection of Amanda, but a word that
I feel like people just don't want to
dive into enough.
>> Okay.
>> Just like when a Republican comes out
and says something and they lose their
job and everyone's like free speech
isn't free,
there's a community of folks who
pride themselves on saying the thing.
>> Mhm.
>> And I think you should pride yourself on
that.
>> Me, Amanda, uh Dominique, we're all part
of that tribe.
Y'all see the girls coming from my neck
every third Sunday when they board in a
slow news week, and I don't give a good
[ __ ] right? I understand that there's
no way in hell I can do the work that I
do and be a fragile daffodil, right? I
have to be somebody who who is willing
to say things that I mean, understanding
the consequences of me saying those
things because
speech might be free, but consequences
are not, right? We we have freedom of
speech, not freedom of consequences.
One more time for the apologist in the
back fanning confusion. We have freedom
of speech, not freedom of consequences.
Again, I am so clear when I have certain
conversations with you guys publicly on
social media that there's a price to pay
in real life.
And I pay that price willingly every
day. It offends me that someone would
act as if they are kindred in that way,
but constantly [ __ ] about the price of
admission. You can't have both.
You can't.
I'm speaking as somebody who's living
this. You can't have both. You can't run
your mouth and expect everybody to love
you.
Either shut up and be a people pleaser
and be loved by all cuz you haven't said
[ __ ] or speak the truth and shame the
devil and recognize the devil might not
invite you to its house.
But you can't have both, and it's
bizarre to me. It's bizarre to be over
40 and still acting like you don't know
what that means.
>> And it's not easy being outspoken. It's
not easy saying something that ruffles
feathers. It's not easy recognizing
[snorts] your privilege in a moment and
using that privilege to to stand up and
speak out. That is not easy, and
you need to know that you will not be
included in certain
>> Amanda didn't respond to a comment. She
made a whole video, love. You might want
to update your your data.
>> things because of that. And
to think that you get to reap the reward
of being outspoken, wear that as a
badge, you know, be the renegade, all
the [clears throat] things, and that
doesn't mean that when the reunion
happens, they don't want you there, or
that doesn't mean that
when the brand is booking people, and
they're and and and and they're looking
at videos you make when you gag somebody
or
and they're just like, oh, I'm I'm cool
on that.
That's what happens.
It's just It's just It's just what the
game is. Um and so, I had to learn early
on to be prepared to reap the benefits
in whatever way that looks, cuz
being excluded is sometime a benefit.
>> Mhm.
>> Sometime a
>> I actually think of men and not being on
the tour as the kindest thing to do. Why
would I want you on the tour feeling
like an outsider because you are, cuz we
don't [ __ ] with you?
I would never invite somebody I don't
[ __ ] with to work with me. Unless I can
literally say, you know what, the Bird
Stop Bridget, I forgive you, I would
never never ever invite someone that I
can't treat well, or that I don't enjoy,
or that I can't Perfect example, when I
work at the shop,
I only work with people that I enjoy,
which means if Danny or Bridget or Mel
or anybody who's working with me at the
shop is having a rough day, I'm the kind
of person who would put down my laptop,
and I'll get up and like, anybody want
some coffee? I will make my people
coffee while they're working if they're
having a work day, right? If you're
having a bad day, the other day the
girls were having a bad day. Life
Mercury retrograde was [ __ ] up
everybody in the shop. I said, you know
what, guys? Bridget was like, yo, I
would love some froyo. You know what,
guys? I'm I'm going to buy y'all some
froyo. We're going to order some froyo.
We're going to turn off all the noise
right now and have a sister moment and
make sure you're good before we get back
to work. If I can't be my full self, if
I can't love on you in the way that's
natural to me,
because I secretly don't [ __ ] with you,
I'm not going to say, come work with me.
It's actually kind of to leave you at
home where it's safe. It's unsafe to be
around people who don't [ __ ] with you.
That's why I'm just like, why are you
guys acting like it's rejection? I think
it's protection not to be in spaces
where you are not warmly welcomed.
>> Rejection is protection, right? Um, to
reap the benefits of what I say, how I
say it, um, y'all will see me sit on
something for a while because I'm like,
what am I prepared to risk it all for?
And that's evolved. At one time I
thought risking it all was worth it
because if I risked it all,
everything would fall into place. And
now I know that's not necessarily true.
So, what I'm willing to risk has
changed. Um, and and so, the insecure
reunion, that's that's Issa [ __ ]
>> Yeah.
>> You
you're not going to go on any platform
after I hired you for my [ __ ]
right?
To then discuss publicly in ways that
I've never discussed issues we have so
on and so forth. And you did it several
several times. And then,
when we're doing a likely not hella
hella funded, hella compensated kind of
reunion moment where
>> Cure Joya was frozen yogurt.
We were all having a really rough day,
so I got everybody Pinkberry. And it it
was
it was just it made sense cuz we I
enjoyed them and I wanted them to have a
good day. I I shared that story as
benign as it is cuz buying people frozen
yogurt is not a big [ __ ] deal, right?
But it's to say that there's a natural
soft and tender way that a community
acts when they all love and trust and
respect each other and feel safe with
each other that is immediately
undermined if there's even one person
who doesn't make sense. We had a one
person working at the shop who had a
nasty attitude. She was fired within
a day. Right? We had another person who
was a little bit off. We we let her go
within 2 days.
I don't just hire people or work with
people who are suited for the job. I
work with people who will not compromise
psychological safety. And from what I've
seen from how lovely and safe and rich
the relationships that Issa has with her
people,
Amy and her knew each other from
Stanford. Like Issa is employing college
friends who are now living their dreams
and working on Netflix and putting out
movies and have first look deals, right?
Like she's an incubator for her friends
to get put on. So yes, if I'm the friend
who's constantly putting my people on
and I put you on and you talk [ __ ]
[ __ ] be happy I didn't say anything
back.
That's the gag is Amanda talked [ __ ] and
Issa's been silent. That already is
grace.
Silence is grace. It took me six years
to finally tell y'all what happened with
Melissa Ford because she wouldn't shut
the [ __ ] up about my name in her mouth.
That six years of silence was grace.
Like come on, guys, enough.
>> just want to come together have a good
time
and maybe [ __ ] only like being with
you ain't a good time. Being with you
was work. And that be like that
sometimes.
>> [clears throat]
>> And you're not invited.
I don't I don't It It does Does it feel
good? No. I'm not saying it's I'm not
saying you can't feel like oh, that
doesn't feel good. And also,
we got to make informed choices.
>> Mhm.
>> That's That's what it That's That's what
That's where it's always been, but
that's what it really is now because
people ain't got time for that. So yeah.
>> And to you academics who are writing
long threads about how from a social
justice perspective, Issa owes it to
Amanda and the fans to eat [ __ ] on her
own god damn tour, shut the hell up.
Y'all read bell hooks backwards. Shut
the hell up. That's not how that work.
It is emotionally unintelligent to set
yourself on fire to keep other people
warm. You guys are all asking Issa Rae
to set herself on fire to keep Amanda
Seales warm. It's [ __ ] I'm sorry.
It's It's pure This is not even a gray
for me. This is black and white
[ __ ]
>> Oh, I think that people should think
better and this that and the third. No,
that's that lady [ __ ] That's the
benefit of making your [ __ ] is that it's
your due choice. You can do what you
want to do.
And that's that's That's the lesson we
all need to think about.
The girls are The girls are getting
invited somewhere and then you come home
and then you [ __ ] all over the place and
then you're like, "Well, they didn't
invite me." Of course they didn't invite
you back. You talked about them people
like like a
When I come online and I wax somebody,
I'm fully prepared for what that what
that may bring to me. You ain't ever
You're never going to see me get on here
and boohoo and cry because I've said
this this this and then they were just
like, "Oh, we don't [ __ ] with
Dominique."
>> By the way, this is Dominique who again
has had nothing but a pleasant
interaction with Amanda Seales, has no
vendetta against Amanda Seales, has
publicly said sometimes y'all dogpile on
her, which I agree. Sometimes, even
though Amanda's not perfect, sometimes
you guys do dogpile on her, right? But,
someone Even people who have pleasant
interactions with Amanda think this is
wild. So, this is not about, "Oh my god,
we're against Amanda." It just doesn't
make any [ __ ] sense.
>> You're never going to see that. Ever.
We're too old. Like, in your 20s? Maybe.
Early 30s? Possibly.
But, on the flip side, Amanda will You
get in her comments and say something,
I've heard she'll block you. She
understands protecting your peace away
from things that
>> Ooh, that's a good point, Dominique. You
ate with this. Dominique, you ate with
this. Amanda blocked me
for having a And I'm I'm going to I
included I didn't even know Dominique
had said this, but Amanda blocked me for
having a fair but critical take on her
using autism as an excuse not to take
accountability for her actions. As
somebody who has been diagnosed with
autism, I took great offense That's what
my birthday. Watching her use autism as
an excuse not to apologize for impact,
even if it was unintentional.
And she blocked my ass.
So, let me get this straight. Someone
has a reasonable, nuanced, fair, yet
critical take on you.
And you block them. You are constantly
blocking people to protect your peace.
But, Esha Ray doesn't get to do the same
thing?
Make that How's that anything other than
hypocrisy? Dominique, you ate with that.
>> You don't want to have around. So, if
that's how she moves in her space, why
would other people not move? And I'm not
And I don't think I've seen Amanda
cry about it. I know she did the
Netflix, you know, thing where, you
know, with the Tiffany thing and I think
that was her nod towards it to amp up
her fan base. But, no.
Issa's protecting her peace the same way
Amanda does every day.
>> Hello.
>> Ain't no fun when the rabbit got the
gun.
>> You be talking about
>> Oh, wait. Somebody cursed the whole
>> Wait. Oop.
>> I I added this cuz it it looked like a
part two, but I didn't realize I just
realized from looking at it. Someone
said, "You just be talking about
everything and saying nothing. You're
wrong about this, Dominique. You should
have just sat this one out. Just loud
and wrong. This may be may have
be how you got your coins, but you're
wrong." Oh, they attacked Dominique for
being someone who's cool with Amanda for
still telling the truth.
>> [sighs]
>> You know how I feel
when y'all act like black women can't
hold each other accountable because who
the [ __ ] else that can? Y'all know how I
feel about this.
My version of of women's empowerment is
not black women acting as bad and as
unchecked as the men we once feared.
Allowing black women to behave badly to
me is not improvement.
It's not. So, the fact that y'all
attacked Dominique for that incredibly
fair take where she didn't even talk
[ __ ] Yeah, y'all just want to be mad.
Y'all If If If Dominique's getting
attacked, now I get some This is why I'm
so happy that I don't ever look myself
up.
>> My everything and saying nothing. You're
wrong about this, Dominique. You should
have just sat this one out. Just loud
and wrong. This may be how you get your
coins, but you're wrong." And they go on
to say like Issa's doing is doing wrong,
team Amanda.
I've never watched an episode of
Insecure.
>> Ooh.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] about that.
>> OOH. WAIT. WAIT A MINUTE.
>> [laughter]
>> WAIT.
OKAY, NOW I FEEL BETTER ABOUT WHEN Y'ALL
BE PISSING me cuz y'all be making me
seem like like like crazy for having a
valid reaction to a bunch of [ __ ]
Y'all don't PISSED OFF DOMINIQUE.
>> [laughter]
>> OKAY, I DIDN'T REALIZE Y'ALL PISSED her
off like this. Go off, sis. They got you
[ __ ] up. Yo, this Mercury retrograde
is wild. This is This Mercury retrograde
is The last time Mercury retrograde was
this bad and was in Cancer cuz you know
Cancer's very emotional and violent.
Shout out to the Cancers who healed. But
because Cancer's so emotional and
violent, the last time Mercury
retrograde was in Cancer was in 2020.
So, these are like pandemic era like
fist-a-cuffs that we are seeing right
now.
Y'all don't pissed off Dominique Morgan.
She be on some Kumbaya [ __ ] since she
came out. Y'all got You got You got my
good sis upset. Dominique, I'm I have
your back on this one. Who do we need to
fight?
>> What specifically am I wrong about? I
said that when somebody owns and runs
their [ __ ] you cannot be surprised when
you use your free will, as you have the
right to, share your lived experience,
as you have the right to, and they don't
invite you.
That's what I said.
And then I went on to say
use myself as an example of knowing that
when you say things, you will not be
included in certain things, and that's a
consequence of the free speech component
where it's not free of consequences. Or
again, I think I specifically said in
the video
that um you not
>> Well, thank you. My my my team has made
it clear that I I have to have
professional thumbnails. I know some of
you don't like change, but baby, it's
it's here to stay, child. I'm trying to
be a professional. But yeah, y'all got
Dominique mad and I don't blame her.
>> Being invited is sometimes the covering
you need. You know what I'm saying? Like
separation is protection.
I'm not team anybody.
>> She's not.
As I said in the opening, I I've met
Amanda. I spent time with her.
I have not had any bad interactions with
her.
Truth always. And I'm sure you're
probably a bot or I don't know.
But I'm making this video because I
don't have the capacity to type it out.
>> Oh yeah, she is a cancer. Yikes, so she
must be fighting for her life right now
during this retrograde.
>> And
I don't like when y'all are rude as
[ __ ] You would never speak to me like
that to my face.
>> Never.
>> It's like, [ __ ] watch your mouth. Who
are you talking to?
Especially when I was very
intentional about my words.
>> Yep.
>> I didn't say she shouldn't have said
what she said. I didn't say I'm saying
that
if you invite if somebody has said
something and I don't like I don't like
what they said. I don't like how they
said it. I don't give a [ __ ] whether it
was the worst or not. It's my [ __ ]
>> Yep.
>> A [ __ ] can scratch their ass in
China right now and I can be like, you
scratch your ass in China, you can never
come into my house in Atlanta. AND
THAT'S
>> [laughter]
>> OH.
IT'S SO CATHARTIC SEEING Dominique react
to y'all the way I react to y'all
because I'm going to be honest with
y'all, it has been thousands of nasty
messages since this retrograde.
Thousands. For those of you like, Blue,
why have you been calling people stupid
lately? You don't ever call anybody
stupid. Cuz it's gotten that stupid.
It This last month I have gotten
thousands of nasty Even today, I'm one
of Last year I got dragged by Shelley
and Ace fans for being team Nickalandria
and always having Nickalandria's back.
Do you know that when I announced that
we were going to go live talking about
the alleged split, a bunch of
Nickalandrians cussed me out?
Baby, I took bullets for Nickalandria
last year. Nothing about how I've
treated Nickalandria would tell you that
I would treat them with anything other
than grace AND FAIRNESS. WHY AM I
getting Y'all just want to fight.
I'm so happy Dominique is having this
moment with y'all so y'all know that I'm
not crazy. People have been nasty and on
one.
We're again, the upside down, child.
>> right? Cuz it's my [ __ ]
Or I also said Amanda runs her [ __ ] the
the way. You can say something wrong in
her comments and she's blocking you.
>> Yep.
>> Does she have to have a reason? No,
because it's her [ __ ]
>> Wait, one of our Chinese fans said,
"China know how I get in it."
Shout out to our international viewers.
>> [laughter]
>> Ain't no [ __ ] coins from threads, you
dummy.
>> Come to
>> Wait, she said, "Ain't no [ __ ] coins
from threads, you dummy."
>> Well, you see how Dominique called you a
dummy. Guys, if you
when you attack someone who is
intelligent and intentional and nuanced
with their language, who has done their
research and their homework, and who is
making it a point to be fair, and you
are digging a booger out your nose and
eating it while typing with your left
hand and making no sense being nasty, at
some point they're going to call you
they're going to call you stupid.
I promise you, if any of you
switch places with me, you would have
started calling people stupid much
earlier. It took a lot for me to get
here. Yes? So, just know y'all
the girls like to tussle, but guess
what? The social commentators can tussle
back. We're in entering a time where
being able to talk [ __ ] to somebody
who's a public figure and not getting
checked publicly, those days are over.
We're all tired.
Speaking of being tired, and speaking of
everybody having the right to create
their own version of peace, I tell
people all the time if I am posting
things that you find jarring and you
cannot process and it's [ __ ] up your
day, please block me. Well, Amanda
Seales took that [ __ ] seriously. I'm
about to play you the the the the
podcast clip that that I did the day
after my birthday cuz again, April 24th,
2024, Amanda Seales and Sharon uh Sharon
um
Shannon Sharpe dropped their their
episode on my [ __ ] birthday, ruined
my dinner cuz everybody wanted to watch
that [ __ ]
The next day we had to we had to tape a
very special episode of Blue Centric for
my birthday, and of course that became
the topic. It hijacked the [ __ ]
podcast episode. I released a clip of
everybody sharing their points of view.
And the very next morning Amanda blocked
me. So let's all see. Amanda wants to
talk big [ __ ] about Issa for years and
still be on the tour. Let me show you
what I said that got me blocked. I'm
going to show I'm I'm I'm I'm on some of
my own goddamn receipts. By the way, for
those of you who have been waiting a
year for that infamous worst love life
story time ever, right? My biggest
dating disaster was my first viral
stream and it's how I became a streamer.
The one-year anniversary is coming up
next week. I think maybe this week or
next week. Well, because the Wi-Fi is
funky, maybe next week. We'll see. But
sometime in the month of July, we're
going to revisit that story time. I took
it down 6 months ago, so it's not
visible. I'm going to bring it back up
and a year later react to it. Why am I
bringing this up? Because all the
[ __ ] who betrayed me that I
talked about in that video are in this
clip I'm about to show. So for anybody
who knows
about the betrayal of 2024,
I'm preparing you to see those
[ __ ] on my page for the first
time in a year.
Florence,
Gio, all of y'all prepare be prepared.
You're going to see them pop in the
screen, but it's only for a couple of
minutes, okay? I'm I'm going to actually
calm down cuz I don't even want to see
them myself. All right, let's let's play
the clip that got me banned by Amanda
Seales. So you can see the kind of
critiques that she bans. It doesn't have
to be egregious.
>> A very special
>> Live from the you know
>> [clears throat and laughter]
>> I thank you for joining the show.
>> Thank you so much for having me.
>> Amanda is a brilliant woman. Amanda is a
socially conscious woman. Amanda has
dedicated herself to blackness. She
almost has no incentive now Do you see
how many um
valid moments of acknowledging her
impact that I started with?
She didn't even care. But let me
continue. Now, to listen to feedback
because she's been mishandled in public
and has a diagnosis to fall back on. And
so what I'm scared is any opportunity
that we had for Amanda Seales to ever
say I [ __ ] up. I got it wrong. It was
me. I think we might have watched it fly
away with with her last damn. That makes
me sad.
>> Now that she has this new found fan base
from autism and neuro divergency.
There's those people who like you've
been so excellent at what you do, but
you've sort of like excelled your way
out of the tier of like normal human
life and regulation. Like when she told
us the like the origin stories of her at
Sirius XM, she was missing little
details here and there like this is what
you're supposed to do before you do a
thing. There were many moments in her
life where she was really like
>> [ __ ] these rules.
>> No rules, no system, no parents. I'm
just doing what I do. You're living a
life like that and then you're getting
smarter and smarter and I don't think
that anybody who's really living like
that who's against the rules is learning
to be with the rules.
>> Are you calling her a white man?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean
>> Good one.
>> I think she's [laughter] a very grounded
super villain. That's what it is.
>> Ooh, I love that. I love that.
Every villain got a origin story though.
>> Everybody loves an anti-hero.
>> Every neuro divergent person I know is
like cuz she described a feeling that I
relate to, she must be new savior.
>> Oh, no, no, that's not how that works.
>> When human beings they just need to see
somebody who looks anything close
claiming the thing that they've been
ashamed of and they call them God.
>> She has a purpose that she stepped into
and she does a lot of great things
particularly when it comes to speaking
out against what's happening in
Palestine, X, Y, and Z. And she still
has an ego that has not been fully
checked in a safe way. It's always in an
unsafe and blatantly bad way where you
even wouldn't want your worst enemy to
be treated like that.
>> Two things can be right at the same
time. I think that Amanda has proven
that she is difficult to work with and
she's not a sweet girl. She's also very
talented. She's also very smart. It's
very easy for her to do word Olympics
with people
>> and talk them into a corner.
>> And Shannon was like, I don't know about
all that. I just know you're not
supposed to talk back to grown people.
>> It's like [laughter] you have to take
the valedictorian head off and be like,
let me talk to everybody.
>> And I'm not saying that Shannon is the
sharpest tool in the bag. Like there was
a lot of times where she
>> Nobody has ever said that.
>> [laughter]
>> We're like, no Shannon, THAT'S RACISM.
MY MAMA AIN'T WHITE THOUGH.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN DOING WHITE THINGS.
>> SHE MARRIED A WHITE MAN. My daddy is
black.
>> [laughter]
>> When I watched the Amanda Seales
interview, I was very aback how autism
was almost used as an excuse to never
take accountability for how you
co-create a situation. To never
acknowledge that maybe, even though you
felt bad, you weren't actually being
attacked. To never say, "Hey, people
think and see things differently, and
how I perceive it and how it was
intended aren't always the same thing."
I don't want a world of neurodivergent
people who think that our brain function
is an excuse to demonize everybody in
our lives. You can be autistic and still
be accountable because intention doesn't
negate impact. If you hurt somebody,
being autistic alone for you not to say
sorry.
You can be autistic and still be
accountable for your impact. Being
autistic alone is not an excuse not to
say sorry.
That's what offended Amanda Seales and
made her block me.
The person who blocked me for saying
something that objectively reasonable is
confused why years of biting the hand
that's literally feeding you would get
her disinvited. I'm sorry. I'm calling
[ __ ]
You're being so understanding and
offering actual constructive criticism
as a diagnosed autistic person.
I still got blocked. So, imagine being
fragile enough
to block someone about a reasonable
critique that highlighted your impact,
your value, and all the good things
about you while also stating that you've
been unfairly abused, so now that you
have this this thought of a diagnosis,
you might lose incentive to hold
yourself accountable and fall into
victim speak, which is what I say about
everybody. I said it about Shamir just
last week, right? The person who's
saying all that and saying, "Hey, babe,
just cuz you're autistic doesn't mean
you don't have to say sorry. You still
have to say sorry if you get diagnosed."
Blocked.
But, you were supposed to go on tour
with you.
I'm sorry, y'all.
If you still think she needs to be
invited for that tour after all of this,
we're not kindred cuz it's it's it's
some [ __ ] At some point, you got to
call a thing by its name.
>> I can't friend at first I was
>> So, this is Amanda
feigning confusion. Amanda put out a
video after she made that First of all,
I'm going to say this.
I'm about to take accountability for a
hot moment that I that I learned from
Joe Budden. I know, it's crazy. Joe
Budden taught me something that I had
not thought of.
Look, I tell you all the time, even when
it's weird and inconvenient, I'm willing
to admit when I've learned new [ __ ] and
I've evolved in the way I see things.
I was on the Joe Budden podcast
and we were discussing Meg the Stallion
and y'all know I was there to defend Meg
against the way that men speak about her
as if she's not human.
At one point, the men said, "Yes, Blue,
you're making great points and
can we all just admit that it's possible
that if you have gotten your heart
broken
and you come out with a sensational
statement on your stories that somebody
cheated on you and broke your heart
even if everything you said it was true
technically
you're weaponizing your fan base against
that person and getting ahead of it so
that they're attacking that person on
your behalf. Can you just admit that?"
And I got quiet and I sat with that.
And I said, "Well, Meg's had an un
you know, a very
uh young generation relationship with
the with the the press where she's
constantly sharing in a way that I
wouldn't as a millennial.
Right?"
But then I thought about it and I said
"No, there's a point.
I know
that when I was working at not working
at, when I had an Airbnb for 5 years
whenever something dastardly would
happen Oh, by By I still owe you guys
the Airbnb story. Added to the
storytime, Florence.
Whenever I would have a [ __ ] up
situation with Airbnb
and I would call customer service and
say, "This person has rented out my
downstairs area for 2 months and they're
doing X, Y, and Z and I need them out
and I need a refund." and Airbnb would
give me their ass to kiss. I always knew
the second I went to Twitter and told
Twitter that Airbnb had sent somebody
horrible to my house,
they would immediately send me a refund.
In fact, to this day, literally just
last week somebody I knew was running an
Airbnb and was complaining that she
couldn't get a refund and I said, "Baby,
if you ever want to get a refund from
Airbnb, just go on Twitter and shout
them out. The minute you involve the
public, they're forced to do what you
want." and I heard myself say it to her
and suddenly the conversation I had with
Joe 2 months ago clicked and I was like,
"Oh, shit."
"Oh, [ __ ] He's not wrong."
I know that if I can't get someone to
react the way that I want, in my case it
was Airbnb was a conglomerate, yes, and
what's awkward is me and one of the
co-founders went to high school
together. Shout out to you, Nate. Y'all
you probably [ __ ] hate me now. But, I
knew that if Nate and them would [ __ ]
with my money
at the Airbnbs, all I had to do was go
on Twitter and In fact, one time I had
an Airbnb situation that was so bad,
Black Lives Matter retweeted it. They
gave me a full refund and paid for my
Thanksgiving hotel stay, right?
Thank you. I have to When people are
right, I have to eat it.
I said, "Oh my god, even though I have
Meg's back,
objectively and technically speaking,
when you do go on social media
to speak about a grievance that no one
else is talking about, in that moment
you are objectively weaponizing public
sentiment whether you have good
intentions or bad intentions, neutral
intentions, or don't even recognize what
you're doing, that is objectively what
is happening.
You see, I can give you book credit.
You all thought I was going on that show
to teach them something, they actually
ended up teaching me something.
Yeah, he would Joe was right. I can't
believe I'm saying Joe Budden you were
right, child. I could eat it.
I I can eat it. I can eat it. I'm woman
enough to [ __ ] eat it, right? So, in
the same way that Joe opened my eyes to
how
in his case he was talking about women
versus men and how sometimes men feel
who don't have platforms, who are dating
women who have big platforms, almost
feel held captive by that. I still think
that the way that they were talking
about um Meg was misogynistic and I'm
happy that they were open They're open
to learning from me, too. So, we learn
from each other, which I think is a
healthy conversation, right? In the same
way that I know they learned something
from me, I took away that as a valuable
lesson about being more cognizant about
weaponizing public sentiment. I know
that if somebody does me dirty right now
and I call out their name, the Blue
Crew, people who love me, people who
care about even people who loathe me,
but low-key know that I'm an honest
[ __ ] they're going to listen to me,
right?
I'm saying all that to say,
I don't believe this video.
Because of what Joe taught me, I'm going
to have to admit that Amara is on some
[ __ ] in this video. Because in this
video, her premise is, "Oh, I just
posted that little Netflix thing to be
fun. No part of me thought it was going
to create a public stir."
[ __ ]
respectfully. Well, I'm blocked, you
can't even see me. No part of me thought
it was going to create a public stir,
even though I intentionally included
screen grabs of public comments in my
[ __ ] video.
How does that work?
But since y'all care so much about
Tiffany and me being on the tour, since
you guys want to hear from me so bad,
I'll talk about it.
Girl.
You posted that video because you were
salty and you wanted to
be trending and you wanted your name to
take over all of the marketing for
Insecure's tour so that every time
people thought about the tour, they
would know you weren't going to be on
there and that your folks could attack
those who were excited about coming and
dim their light since you couldn't be
included. Can we all just call a thing
by its name?
Come on.
Thank you. The tea is cold.
So, you're about to make this video and
tell us, "Well, I didn't I was just
joking. I was just playing. But, since
y'all want since y'all miss Tiffany
Haddish so bad, LET'S TALK ABOUT GIRL.
Now that Joe's opened my eyes, cuz I
can't unsee it.
Now even when I open my mouth, I got to
be careful cuz I might I don't want to
weaponize the blue crew against
somebody. I got to be intentional. I got
to Even in fact, that place that I
stayed,
the for those of you who saw my um Love
Island uh breakdown about the real
reason why Love Island is weird this
year. By the way, that video did really
well and I'm so happy cuz I'm I think of
all the Love Island videos I've done. If
you haven't seen any of my Love Island
videos, the only one that I would
hardcore recommend is the real reason
why Love Island is so weird. And when I
made that video, the first 30 minutes is
me talking about my horror story of
paying for an oceanfront luxury hotel,
paying $2,000 to spend 48 hours at a
luxury hotel just to pull up to a motel.
When I was telling that story, I
normally would have just said their name
and don't ever [ __ ] go here. And I
thought about what Joe said and I was
like, "Blue,
even though the hotel was in some
[ __ ] the employees are nice. I
don't think they're getting paid enough.
I don't want to say their name unless
they pissed me off." I They They haven't
pissed me off bad enough for me to call
out their name because now I'm aware
about the the impact of my platform and
I don't want to intentionally have that
staff be getting a bunch of phone calls
from the Blue Crew. If I say somebody's
name, I understand you guys might hit
them up and I'm okay with it because
what they've done is egregious enough.
In my mind, the hotel was in the Okay,
the hotel was egregious enough, but the
employees who I know would get those
calls were not egregious enough. I
intentionally didn't mention their names
as a kindness, as a grace. The same way
I still tipped that bellhop even though
he was an [ __ ] to me.
Do you know a couple of days ago, shout
out to her, she's watching again, I get
a DM from Laverne Cox.
Laverne Cox says, "Bitch, I was catching
up with Love Island, so I was watching
your video cuz I wanted to learn from
you.
I'm so sorry about what happened to you
at that hotel. Sorry, that motel."
And we're having this cute little
exchange via DM. Laverne Cox is so
[ __ ] lovely, by the way. Very lovely.
And I'm like, "See, what if I had said
that motel?"
You never know who's watching. What if I
had called out the the motel by name,
right? Not a hotel, it's a motel. So,
that's just to say,
Amanza has been at this way longer than
me.
I might have just fully sat with the
impact of my words online when it comes
to calling out the shaming the devil
that are lay people. But Amanza is not
new to this [ __ ]
Wasn't she on My Cousin Skeeter or some
[ __ ] She's been doing this since she
was seven or eight.
So, again, it's dishonest as [ __ ] to
make a video
where you're going to pretend that you
didn't know this was going to happen.
I thought you said I thought your
tagline was I be knowing. How is it you
be knowing but you could miss the
obvious? You can't have both. Either you
be knowing or you or you miss the
obvious, yes? So, she's doing this video
under the premise that I'm only doing it
for y'all, so let's have a teachable
moment.
To that young man who walked up to me at
the uh Where the Black People At party
in Miami in 2024 and said, "You remind
me of Amanda Seales' uh non-evil twin."
I was deeply offended when he said that
because I don't want want to be compared
to anybody and you don't have to
disparage her in order to
make me feel like you appreciate my
work. And however,  this video
very specifically
This video very specifically is where
that statement makes sense because you
guys, what have I been talking about in
these lives since 2019 when I started
doing them on Instagram and then moved
them over to to YouTube last year? For 7
years, I have been doing
uh lives on social media about a lack
mindset versus an abundant mindset. So,
how do you think I felt
when I open up this video that's on some
[ __ ] and Amanda is using the premise
of a lack mindset versus abundance
mindset in order
to excuse her behavior.
I don't want to say I was offended, but
watching the kind of work that I do be
used for personal gain to teach people
the wrong things, it it it pissed me
off.
It pissed me off. So, we're about to
watch For all of you who have been
watching Blue Centric live before we
were even called that back when we were
doing it on Instagram,
you're about to watch Amanda talk about
lack and abundance, but it sounds very
different from when I do it. This does
feel like some evil twin type [ __ ]
>> Like, y'all are taking this insecure
thing too far. Like, it's
it I mean, it's my experience.
Otherwise, it felt like what's the
point? However, seeing the visceral
response from fans brought me
>> Seeing the visceral response that you
courted on purpose. What are you talk
Okay.
I'm going to Sorry, I'm not going to
interrupt.
There's a certain level of [ __ ]
where the stench gets so loud it's hard
for me to keep my mouth shut, but I'm
I'm I'm I'm going to do my best to shut
the [ __ ] up and let let her let her spin
this in a way that I find incredibly
manipulative and harmful.
>> all the way back to when I took the
black popular culture class that
Professor Donna Aye Davis taught at SUNY
Purchase, and she really drilled
that art for black folks, particularly
in the United States, is not simply just
about entertainment. It is political
because
>> I agree. Art is political for people of
color and marginalized people who lack
representation. I agree with that.
>> it is our representation and in our own
voice. That is something that we rarely
get. So, our characters and our stories
are not simply just meant to entertain.
They are literally meant as proof of
life. And so,
>> Yes, I agree. You guys, I'm going to
keep on stopping to say where I agree so
you can spot where the [ __ ] shows
up.
Because the most dangerous liar is a
liar who is hiding behind the truth.
One more time for the folks in the back,
and we will play the dogs after this
segment cuz I'm pissed.
The most dangerous liar is a liar who is
hiding behind the truth.
>> That made me say, "Okay, I need to talk
about this further, but in a greater
context."
Let's talk about
the difference between
lack and abundance.
>> Oh my god.
I'm sorry. Amanda Seales talking about
lack and abundance is doing my head in.
As somebody who's been teaching about
this for 20 years, and this is literally
like the cornerstone of all my work,
I'm shaking. Sorry, I'm going to let her
cook. I'm going to let her cook. I'm
going to let her get this off.
I'm let I'm going to let her use all the
valid points that I use for good, and
let her use them for personal gain, and
just shut the [ __ ] up, okay? Blue, shut
the [ __ ] up. I love you, Blue. Just shut
up. Let the girl talk. I'm going to let
her Sorry, I'm going to let her talk.
I'm going to let her talk. Go ahead.
>> Lack conversation
is why would Amanda expect to be invited
to the Insecure reunion?
An abundance conversation is why were
amends not made so that Amanda would be
present at the Insecure reunion?
>> [ __ ]
Uh [ __ ] Uh [ __ ]
Uh [ __ ]
>> I think I put that in there cuz I know I
was going to get upset.
Her premise is that it's a lack
conversation to hold her accountable.
It's lack
to hold her accountable.
>> [snorts]
>> Amanda still is teaching millions of
people who follow her and devoted to her
that it's lack to hold people
accountable.
Mhm. Y'all going [clears throat] to have
to give me a second cuz this It's not
easy to offend me. This is just annoying
me. I get annoyed all the time, but it's
not easy to offend me. Yeah, this is
this this this this this this is
offensive.
Uh for those of you who follow Amanda
and believe this, accountability is not
lack. Her premise is it's lack to hold
her accountable. It's abundant to hold
Issa accountable instead and say, "Why
didn't Issa bend over backwards to make
her feel comfortable after she talked
[ __ ] about her after catching her
check?"
>> [sighs and snorts]
>> I'm going to let this play. Ultimately,
a reunion tour for a TV show would be
all about pleasing the fans of that
show. That's the goal. And I So,
ultimately, as a creator, Issa Rae
should only care about pleasing her fans
and not care anything about the safety
of her and the other creatives who have
dedicated a a decade of their life to
the show who also need to be held safe.
So, [ __ ] Issa, [ __ ] the creatives, [ __ ]
Penny, [ __ ] everybody else associated,
[ __ ] Emmy, Yvonne Orji, and all my
friends who are good humans who've never
said a When I tell you nobody that I
know from Insecure has ever said a a
single bad word about Amanda, even when
I'm around. When I get around, they get
quiet. I get mad like, "Yo, that's
[ __ ] up." And they'll be like, "Blue,
Godspeed to her.
We wish her the best." In private.
WHEN I TELL YOU NOBODY on that team
talked [ __ ] about Amanda Seales, even
when there are no cameras, they show
this girl so much grace. I think that's
why I'm getting so mad.
No cameras. Nobody around.
Vow of silence. Nothing but grace.
>> [sighs]
>> It gets to a point It gets to a point It
gets to a point
It get I
I'm going to let this finish so we can
play the dogs.
>> I would suggest that the fans of a show
want to see the characters that they
have aligned with. There are many people
who have said they didn't give a damn
about Tiffany. However, I know, because
I experience it on a regular basis,
there are so many women in particular,
mothers in particular, who very much
aligned with Tiffany's um journey
through postpartum depression and really
connected with me like in person to say
thank you for portraying that in such a
realistic way.
>> Why didn't you think about Tiffany's
impact on women who have gone through
postpartum and how important it was when
you were just getting mad and airing out
personal grievances for nobody other
than yourself then?
If you thought that you had a there was
a moral responsibility to all the black
women who saw themselves in Tiffany, and
you had personal trivial grievances
against your castmates, and you saw that
they had personal trivial grievances
against you, and they shut the [ __ ] up
for the greater good, they shut the [ __ ]
up for the fans. They don't even speak
ill of you behind closed doors because
they just wish you well.
Why didn't you follow suit then? Why do
we suddenly care about Tiffany and her
legacy after you've gotten to run your
mouth?
>> Which is also why, you know, the
performance of stories on speak on
>> Members only is about to start in like
10 minutes cuz I Yeah, we started super
late cuz there was a technical issue,
but we're starting Once this is over,
I'm going to take 10 minutes to pee and
grab a snack and jump in the bed. We're
doing members only from the bed, child.
I'm about I'm about to lay in the bed
for members only. But once we start the
members only, you will know cuz this
will ending and then we'll get a
10-minute break. But let's let her
finish cooking
so I can be done with this.
>> screen is so imperative because people,
humans, we need to be seen. On a larger
scale,
I'm always thinking of how do I show up
in abundance versus lack.
>> The only thing I hate more than a liar
is a liar that thinks I'm stupid.
>> I didn't always think that way. However,
as I have grown, particularly in the
last 3 years, spiritually,
intellectually, communally, that has
definitely been a shift. And the
difference between lack and abundance is
important
because lack is patriarchal and it deals
with the failure to see growth, to see
expansion
on a communal level.
So
abundance, on the other hand, is
matriarchal and is about restoration.
And so the difference is imperative to
how we even view our role in resistance
on a much bigger scale.
While I have you, if you'd like to hear
me talk about things on a abundance
level, you can check out my new radio
show on Tavis Smiley's KBLA Talk 1580.
>> Wait, IS THIS A COMMERCIAL?
SORRY, I DIDN'T GET TO THE END.
SHE SAID ALL that to to as a plug to her
new Okay.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> Grifters going to get my grift child.
Grifters going to grift. Okay.
>> I'll be there every Friday with the
Summer of Seals from 12:00 to 2:00 p.m.
Pacific and 4:00 to 6:00 p.m. Pacific.
And you can check me out by downloading
the KBLA
>> If you want to check out them if you
heard all that and and and you
you feel you feel kindred to her. I'm
not going to be a hater. I I don't want
to take money out of anybody's mouth.
Feel free to
follow whatever the [ __ ] she's plugging.
>> Talk 1580 radio app or listen on
YouTube. When y'all compare me and
compare me to Amanda Seales, it
genuinely
>> I picked this girl because her first
line was when y'all compare me to Amanda
Seales, it genuinely pisses me off. Now,
here's the funny thing. She carries
herself in the same cadence as Amanda
Seales. She actually kind of looks like
her, especially when she smiles.
But she
as someone who gets compared to Amanda
all the time, even she's calling
[ __ ] Do you know how bad it is for
your sons? What does Nicki Minaj say?
Oh, you [ __ ] is my sons. Even people
who are literally walking in your
footsteps are like, Amanda, this is some
[ __ ] Let's Let's hear what Amanda
3.0 got to say about Amanda 1.0.
>> pisses me off on so many different
levels. Like probably my least favorite
comparison ever for a plethora of
reasons, for many reasons. But the main
one is because Amanda Seales is
annoying. And the reason why she's
annoying is because she cannot accept
the fact that she's unlikable. Unlike
her, I know that I'm unlikable. I've
made peace with it. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] if you don't like
me. So, I would never be up here at
boohooing about not being invited
somewhere. I don't give a [ __ ] It's not
going to be fun [ __ ] cuz I'm out
there. I'm the [ __ ] party. I'm the
life of the party. Y'all missing out.
Why would I care that I'm not invited?
Y'all going to Y'all going to be bored
without me. What the [ __ ] And Amanda
Seales can't doesn't understand one
fundamental truth, which is that you
can't be both a [ __ ] and a victim. And
like she tries to teach the
>> Oh, you can't be both a [ __ ] A [ __ ] is
a victim. Say more, young buck. I'm
trying to learn from the youth, y'all.
I'm always trying to look I saw a
KRS-One quote that said, "When the when
the elders" and by elders I uh uh
I'm in my 40s, but in these days the
minute you hit 40, you're an elder
apparently. So, as a young auntie who
could still lay low and spread it wide,
I like to listen to the younger girls
cuz they keep me they keep me present.
And he said, "When you're older, listen
to people who are younger because they
keep you fresh. And when you're younger,
listen to people older because they help
you skip steps and get there faster." It
makes sense for both sides to listen to
each other. So, I want to hear what the
young folks have to say. I intentionally
found somebody who is young enough to be
my niece cuz I want to hear maybe it's
just my age group that thinks Amanda is
some [ __ ] Maybe the the the babies
the Z the Gen Zs and Alphas like it.
Baby, they call her out names more than
we are.
Just not aging well. The babies are the
babies are are clocking the [ __ ]
too.
>> line. It does not exist. You cannot be
both. You can't be both the bully and
the survivor. It doesn't
>> Ooh, you can't be both the bully and the
survivor.
Yes.
Okay.
>> work. No. So, when you use your platform
to be loud as [ __ ] call people out
and be like, "I don't [ __ ] with them.
Did it does not occur." But then turn
around and want to whine and cry that
they're not inviting you places. You
were talking [ __ ] about them. Why the
[ __ ] would they invite you anywhere? Are
you stupid? Like, what the [ __ ] And you
keep bringing it up is lame as [ __ ] You
don't like them. It seems like they
don't like you more. Hence why they
don't invite you anywhere. Hence why
they don't bring you up. Hence why they
forget that you exist. Stop bringing
them up. It's pathetic. Oh my god, have
some [ __ ] self-esteem. Have some
self-respect. Have some [ __ ] dignity.
This [ __ ] is embarrassing to watch.
Like babe, the bridge is burnt to a
crisp. Let it go.
>> Now, how must it feel to see somebody
who looks just like you 20 years ago
saying that [ __ ] I ain't say none of
that.
I I ALMOST FELT BAD, but I was NICER
THAN HER.
>> [laughter]
>> WELL. WELL. All right, guys. We're going
to pivot to Cheyenne Bryant. Oh, Jesus.
I'm doing a lot today. To go from Amanda
to Sio to Cheyenne Bryant, this is the
Lord's work. Yeah, you know what, guys?
I'm going to make a cocktail before I do
the after show.
Let's all make for those of you who
drink. If you're sober, please respect
that. But for those of you who drink
alcohol safely, let's make cocktails and
put on our bathrobes for the aftershow.
Okay, this this is the last segment,
guys, before we take a break and pivot
to the aftershow for the members.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Of course I am Bryant You guys, this
this this trend is supposed to be 10
seconds. Why is Why is Cheyenne Bryant
just hitting replay on the music for
like a minute while she gets dressed
like [ __ ] Mr. Rogers' Neighborhood
taking off his shoes and his sweater.
Sh- This woman has so many narc-
narcissistic leanings and traits. She
can't She's like, "No, I need more than
10 seconds to troll."
Run that back eight more times while I
get dressed.
Even Amanda only did 6 to 10 seconds.
Cheyenne said, "No, I want to I want
60."
I think I think unintentionally, I was
doing these in chronological order.
First, I saw Tia, then I saw Amanda,
then I saw Cheyenne. I think I might
also be doing them in narcissistic trait
order. I think it's almost like a
gradient of narcissistic traits. And you
guys, I'm saying narcissistic because
anybody can be narcissistic, but you
need a trained professional to diagnose
you as a narcissist, right? So, the -ic
means it's accessible to all of us.
I think if we had a narcissistic just
gradient, I think the lightest hand is
Tia.
I feel very comfortable saying that. I
think a big old thick intermediate
dollop is Amanda. Intermediate going
towards advanced. I think Cheyenne
Bryant is a master of narcissistic
behavior.
I think she's the grand poobah of this
narcissistic [ __ ]
So, [snorts] it's funny that we're going
in order.
It's funny Somebody said why they all
light skin child? I don't know. I just
work here.
I'm I'm not I'm not doing nothing
against the light skin ladies. They just
all happen to look like they related. I
just work here, okay?
Let's Let's Let's see what it says cuz
everybody else has a short one. Hers
says, "When Netflix does a documentary
on Dr. Cheyenne Bryant, episode 1 will
ask, is she really a doctor? Episode 2
through 10 will investigate why complete
jealous envious haters try to prove she
wasn't."
You guys, everybody else is making a
joke about a Netflix documentary.
Cheyenne Bryant is making a joke about a
10-part limited series and she wants us
to read her outline. I I can't.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> You can't make this [ __ ] up. I'M SO
SORRY.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> SHE'S NOT WELL.
SO, I'm going to just go I'm going to I
was going to wait until we're done to go
to the bathroom. I don't mind peeing
through this. I'm about to take a
bathroom break while I am Bryant
terrorizes the rest of you. I'll be
right back.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Is this my camera?
Oh, is this my camera?
Oh, this is my camera.
>> [music]
>> Wait, I came back from the bathroom and
washed my hands and she was STILL GOING?
OKAY.
>> [laughter]
>> WAIT.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. I PEED, washed my
hands, walked back and she was still
going.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm so sorry.
Somebody said it's crack.
>> [laughter]
[laughter]
>> I'm sorry.
Okay. Y'all
>> [laughter]
>> You can she's wearing
Okay, I'm so sorry, guys. This is
ridiculous.
Somebody [laughter]
said I will never forget blueprints.
At some point when when I went to wash
my hands, I said, "That can't be the
same music playing."
>> [snorts]
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
Well, let's see how Maybe the 10-part
series is this. Maybe this is the
10-part series. Is she dressed yet?
>> [music]
>> Oh.
>> The The folks that pissed me off today.
The folks that pissed me off today.
Because, BABY, WE FORGOT ABOUT HER.
LET'S not even sit here and act like we
like really really
remember. Like, we forgot about her. We
have moved on from her.
>> So, who do we have to blame for this?
Jeff, the internet? Having a wall full
of honorary degrees and also a patent on
your name is truly diabolical. But, here
she is again, gaslighting us. Now, I
want the people who actually did the
work, who sacrificed, who actually have
those student loan debt, all that, I
want y'all to chime in. Where can you
buy one of these? How do you feel about,
you know, Amazon just selling this and
you can just put on straight out the
box. She didn't even earn it. All she
wanted to show y'all was, "Yeah, I'm
that
>> You guys, not only is it wrinkled, they
did find it on Amazon. It costs $109.
You can buy this off of Amazon.
>> Girl, y'all jealous, okay? It's all
about me. But, once again, people don't
care. That's why she continues to do
what she still got clients, people still
feeding into it. It's not going to
change because she is that girl in her
eyes. It's a delusion for me. Once
again, looking at all those honorary
degrees, I should also blame y'all
schools for giving her honorary degrees.
Y'all part of the problem, too. But,
here we are once again,
uh delusional.
>> Oh, that was a good laugh. You guys,
here's the um
here's the gotcha. She said, "Well,
[ __ ]
I's a doctor now." No, you had $109 plus
tax.
The I don't
baby,
if you have a hundred and and let's say
$12, depending on how much you pay for
shipping and handling, sometimes Amazon
Prime is free. For $112, you too can be
just as much of a Dr. Shayne Bryant is.
>> What the violets means?
>> It's not even the right shade of blue.
>> Oh, and then the people who actually
have the degree she lied about said it's
the wrong shade of blue. Yikes.
Not as Shayne. So, here's the thing,
when you do a thing for real, there's
different norms that only people who
have done it for real know.
Just as like doctorial
is not a degree.
Um the I stands for I made it up. So, in
the same way you'll be adding extra
letters to the degree you didn't get,
you also have on the wrong color. Um
yeah.
Yikes.
Ooh.
And this is somebody who actually has a
degree that Dr. Shine Bright purports to
have and she's like this is what it
looks like when you actually Don't this
look different?
They actually have the school's name
embroidered on the the the lapel. The
colors are rich. It's not giving
Halloween party via Amazon, is it? It's
like she put on a Halloween costume of
somebody who Let me shut up.
This don't look the same.
>> All right, real quick. Let's get into
this Dr. Bryant controversy everybody's
going crazy over in the robe she had on
yesterday. So,
the robe wasn't random. It's a robe
>> It's doctorial gown. The extra I is why
the shade of blue is slightly off. Got
it.
>> from the honorary doctor she received
from United Graduate College and
Seminary in partnership with the Black
Agenda.
She was not the only one honored on that
day. Uh NFL star Ray Lewis also
>> So, by the way, guys, we thought she
bought on Amazon. No, she got it for
free during a this this this ceremony
where they were giving everybody
from everybody from Ray Lewis to Shabba
Ranks was getting a blue gown that day,
unwrinkled in the wrong color. So,
she didn't pay for it. We talking about
if you had $112, she didn't even pay
that much. Well,
>> received an honorary doctor during that
same ceremony.
So, let's debunk one thing. There's no
evidence she bought the robe off Amazon.
It appears to be the regalia from the
honorary doctor ceremony. Second, people
keep saying the colors are wrong because
she's a clinical psychologist, but this
wasn't the regalia for an earned
doctorate in clinical psychology. It was
from an honorary doctorate. Honorary
regalia isn't necessarily tied to the
rece
>> I might say light blue is education.
Okay, thank you for that. Look at this.
We We We so much today. Blood of fly in
the sky. I can go twice Look, it's like
reading Rainbow in this [ __ ] LeVar
Burton needs to call me. Okay, pass the
torch LeVar because we learning so much
today on Blue Centric Live. Light blues
for education.
>> Cipriano's professional field in the way
people are claiming. But that doesn't
answer the bigger question about her
earned doctorate. Those are two
completely different conversations.
My opinion, I think she's strolling.
Every time people start talking, she
gives just enough to keep the
conversation going without fully
answering questions.
>> Yeah.
>> As far as her earned doctorate, I
honestly don't know.
>> [music]
>> I want this lady to go away from us with
this mess.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know why he tickles me so much.
She's like, I want this lady to leave me
alone. I feel like we all feel like
this.
>> You have done everything but just show
the damn degree.
Mind you, there are the wall of degrees
behind [music] you.
You're not going to tell me that one of
the highest level of degrees that you
can get [music] would not be plastered
in the center of
>> That's true.
Why have so many honorary degrees and
not center the big one?
>> all of these degrees. [music]
Like somebody said, you really would
have ate this up if you sat down with
the degree. Once you put this robe on,
[music] then you showed us the degree,
ma'am.
Then I would have pulled this robe up on
Amazon. And the people are saying when
you graduate from a school, there's an
the school embroidery
>> Yeah, the lady who had the real color
for the degree that she was claiming to
have, that beautiful maroon. You guys
saw I noticed there was two really
pretty stitched embroidered like
something like a crest or something from
the school on the lapel. This this this
really Like jokes aside, this actually
is looking like the Party City version
of the real thing.
>> give on the robe. [music]
There's no school embroidery on your
robe.
Leave us alone if you can't produce the
>> We did a video about men defending her.
Feel free to go watch that on the Blue
Centric Live podcast playlist.
>> degree.
>> Hey.
>> [music]
>> For those of you who are saying she
needs to go away, she's not going away.
You know why? Because I found this
video. She's been trying to get put on
for decades. She was in the B2K video.
Did anybody else know Am I new to this?
Am I Am I late to the party?
Yes, an emblem. Thank you, my love.
Apparently,
she was she's been trying to get put on
since the B2 and the K. Omarion and
them.
Little Fizz and BoP and them. She's been
trying to get put on since then. And
there's receipts. Let's see.
>> [music]
>> So, they're rewinding it to show exactly
where she is. That's That's why the
video keeps stopping.
Yes, it's Cheyenne. She's gorgeous.
She's a beautiful girl. I'm not a hater.
That's a beautiful woman. But, she
played a stalker
>> [laughter]
>> I'm so sorry. This is so unserious. She
played a stalker fan
in a B2K video.
>> Bryant.
Yes, that's her. That's her.
That is Cheyenne,
the doctor.
>> Did you know you can essentially buy a
fake doctorate online?
>> By the way, if Cheyenne, if you do want
to improve your hustle, cuz at this
point, [ __ ] if we going to have a
scheme, at least do it correctly, okay?
As somebody who has a you know, a
repertoire of helping people, being a
fixer, um but if you going to do this,
Cheyenne, I need you to take a thousand
dollars out of um
your Bitcoin or your savings account or
your piggy bank. Take a thousand dollars
and spend it on a fake doctorate so we
can finally get this.
For a thousand dollars, you could just
keep lying and and this grift could be
taken to the next level. If you want
some advice, here we go. Yes, guys, I
got to the point where the ladies is
annoying me so bad I'm about to help
her.
>> And I know this cuz the guy used to date
did it from online for like a thousand
dollars. I don't know about this woman
who they're saying she faked her
doctorate, whatever, but I do know I was
seeing this guy in early 20s, so like I
got an excuse. And like while we were
together, like there was nothing there
was no school work, nothing. And then 3
months later, I see on Instagram or like
LinkedIn or something that he is now
going by Dr. Let's call him Williams,
Dr. Williams. And I was like
Also, I'm getting my hair colored right
now, that's why it's wild. And so I
texted him being like, "You weren't
getting a doctorate." And he's like,
"Well, clearly I'm a doctor now." I was
like, "Of what?" He's like, "Theological
studies." This man spelled God with a
lowercase G like all the time.
He didn't know anything about religion.
I'm not being judgy, but like you
literally just bought a doctorate online
for a thousand bucks. Like there are
places online that will do that for you.
Also, this is a Nicole story a dog
scratched me. And people are like, "Oh,
why would you want to buy a doctorate?"
One, people love clout. And two, cuz
he's going over here like talking about
like, "Oh, Dr. Williams said this, Dr.
Williams said that." Like learn from Dr.
Williams. And like he's not doing like
medical stuff, even though now he is
selling peptides. I don't know, early
20s problems. And one of my friends
asked, she was like, "Why would you do
that?" I'm like, "Cuz you can like, you
know, assume authority." Like people are
like, "Oh, this person knows what
they're talking about." Even if there's
a doctorate not in the field of what
they're talking about, you know, people
still assume they're like, "Oh, this
person went and got a doctorate." And
I'm not saying the woman's lying. Like I
honestly have no idea what I'm keeping
up, but I did zoom in on her picture and
one of it was like Harner Harvest
Christian University or something. And I
did see online, like I went to their
site, and like they hand out like
honorary doctors people like to Busta
Rhymes. So
>> Wait, wait, wait.
>> [laughter]
>> Cheyenne, you got you got a
honorary doctorate from a school who was
honoring you and Busta Bus.
Cheyenne, yours is much of a doctorate
as Busta Rhymes.
Busta, what it is right now, I'mma play
that song.
Girl, this at this point this just feels
like comedy.
Somebody said, "Well, why would you
bring back the scrutiny?" Because she as
the most narcissistic person that we've
covered tonight, she's addicted to the
fame and to the attention. She must be
on y'all tongues.
>> Um I don't know, but I just thought that
was interesting cuz like people didn't
know you can buy a doctorate.
>> Wow, that's good.
That's real good. And honestly, I'm
going to block you right now.
THANKS.
YOU GUYS [laughter]
I NEED YOU GUYS TO know
um
look, she was the stalking of me 2K
video, child. We didn't make that up. We
just report the news, okay? But if y'all
want to try on Brian uh you know,
costume for October, Halloween is my
favorite holiday.
Yeah, guys, this is the end of this
portion of it. It is now 8:45 Eastern
Time, 5:45 Pacific. We're going to meet
back here in 15 minutes at 9:00 Eastern,
6:00 Pacific. So, for my Pacific my West
Coast folks, this is perfect time for
y'all. For my East Coast folks, this is
your nightcap. For my folks overseas,
you're either going to watch this in the
replay or you are just up late and said,
"Fuck it, let's do this." Um I will say
this, if you want to be helpful to the
collective, think about hyping this
video after it's done in the replay
section. You can't hype it right now,
you can only hype it in the replay. And
the replay comment for today, cuz you
know what, we love having replay
comments.
I will say the replay comment for today
is sometimes a joke reveals the truth.
Sometimes a joke reveals the truth,
right? The Netflix doc trend was
supposed to be a good kiki, but it seems
that some of the people here, if not all
of them, low-key end up telling
themselves in some degree, shape, or
form. So, yikes.
I'm going to go make a cocktail. I'll
meet you back in the members only in 15
minutes. And when we meet back in
members only, we're going to talk about
Nickal Andria.
I'm going to keep it cute, cuz I've
always kept it cute with Nickal Andria,
so you guys have no reason to think I'm
ever going to be messy. And we're also
going to like do a little watch party
together. I've always wanted to do a
watch party with y'all, and there's
something I really wanted to watch, but
I wanted to have a live reaction. So,
we're going to have a watch party after
we talk about Nickal Andria. More on
that later when we come back. All right,
I'll see you guys at 9:00 Eastern,
um 6:00 Pacific. Love y'all so much.
Please like the live. Please hype it up.
Please do all the things so more people
can see the show. Thank you so much for
coming for another episode of Luscentic
Live. I love y'all. Bye, family.